so are our administrative points for today an assignment 3 is due tonight so
그래서 오늘 우리의 관리 포인트는 할당 3 때문에 오늘 밤은 너무하다
was done that's going to be easier than assignment to ok that's good hopefully
그 희망 좋은 확인에 할당보다 쉽게​​ 될 것 이루어졌다
gives you more time to work on your projects so also remember your
당신도 기억 귀하의 프로젝트를 수행하는 데 더 많은 시간을 제공하여
milestones where were turned in we returned in last week so we're in the
우리가에있어, 그래서 우리 못했습니다 된 이정표가 지난 주에 반환
process of looking through the milestones to make sure those are ok and
사람들은 확인 있는지 확인하기 위해 이정표를 통해보고의 과정과
also we're working on assignment to creating so we should have that done
또한 우리가 만드는 임무에 최선을 다하고 그래서 우리는 그 짓을해야한다
sometime this week or early next week
언젠가 이번 주 또는 다음 주 초
last time we had a whirlwind tour of all the soccer all the common software
마지막으로 우리는 모든 축구의 회오리 바람 투어 모든 일반적인 소프트웨어를했다
packages that people use for deep learning and we saw a lot of code on
사람들이 깊은 학습을 위해 사용하고 우리가 코드를 많이 보았다 패키지
slides and a lot of stepping through code and hopefully that you found it
슬라이드와 당신이 그것을 발견 잘하면 코드를 단계별로 및 많은
useful for your projects today we're going to talk about to other topics
프로젝트에 유용 오늘 우리는 다른 주제에 대해 이야기하는거야
we're gonna talk about segmentation within segmentation there are two
우리가 분할에서 분할에 대한 거 얘기있어 두 가지가 있습니다
subproblems semantic an instant segmentation we're also going to talk
우리는 또한 말할거야 의미 인스턴트 분할을 하위 문제
about soft attention and within soft attention again they're sort of two
에 대한 부드러운 관심과 부드러운주의에서 다시 그들은 일종의 두의 것
buckets that we've divided things into but first before we go into these
우리는 그러나로 일을 분할 한 양동이 우리는이 들어갈 전에 먼저
details I was there something else I want to bring up briefly so this is the
나는 이것이 그래서 간단히 불러하려면 뭔가 다른 세부 사항이 있었다
image classification errors I think at this point in the class you've seen this
이미지 분류 오류가 나는 당신이 보았던 클래스의이 시점에서 생각
type of figure it many times right so in 2012 Alex not 2013 ZF crushed it
그림의 종류가 여러 번 바로 그래서 2012 알렉스 2013 ZF 그것을 분쇄하지
recently Google Matt and later ResNet is sort of help but wonder classification
최근 구글 매트 이상 ResNet 도움 그러나 경이 분류의 일종이다
challenge in 2015 but turns out as of today there is a new image net result so
새로운 이미지 최종 결과가 너무가 오늘로 2015 년에 도전하지만 밝혀
this paper came out last night
이 논문은 지난 밤에 나왔다
so Google actually has now state of the art on image that with 3.08% top 5 error
그래서 구글은 실제로 이미지에 예술의 현재 상태를 갖는다 3.08 %, 상위 5 오차
which is crazy and the way they do this is with this thing that they call in
어떤 미친하고이 작업을 수행하는 방법은에서 부르는이 일을 함께
section before this is a little bit of a monster so I don't want to go into too
이 괴물의 조금 전에 섹션 그래서 나는 너무로 가고 싶지 않아
much detail but you can see that it's this really deep network that has these
많은 세부하지만 당신은이가이 정말 깊은 네트워크의 것을 볼 수 있습니다
repeated modules so here there's the stem the stem is this guy over here a
반복 모듈 그래서 여기 줄기 줄기 거기에 여기에 이​​상이 사람이다
couple interesting things to point out about this architecture are actually may
이 아키텍처에 대해 지적하는 몇 가지 흥미로운 일들이 수도 실제로
use some balance convolutions which means they have no padding so that makes
즉 수 있도록 그들이 패딩이 없음을 의미하는 일부 균형 회선을 사용
every all the math more complicated but they're smart and I figured things out
모든 모든 수학 더 복잡하지만 그들은 똑똑하고 나는 일을 알아 냈
they also have an interesting feature here is they actually have in parallel
그들은 또한 여기에 흥미로운 기능은 실제로 병렬로 가지고있다가
strident convolution and also Max Pooley so they kind of do these two operations
귀에 거슬리는 회선도 최대 Pooley은 그래서 그들은 종류의이 두 가지 작업을 할
and parallel to down sample images and then concatenate the kind of the and
아래 샘플 이미지 평행 다음의 종류와 연결할
another thing is they they're really going all out on these efficient
다른 것은 그들이 정말이 효율적으로 모든 외출하고있다
convolution checks that we talked about a couple lectures ago so as you can see
당신이 볼 수 있도록 우리가 전에 몇 강의에 대해 이야기 회선 점검
they've actually have these asymmetric filters like one by seven and seven by
그들은 실제로 일곱 일곱에 의해 같은 이러한 비대칭 필터를했습니다
one convolutions they also make heavy use of these one-by-one convolutional
하나의 회선 그들은 또한이 하나씩 길쌈을 많이 사용합니다
bottlenecks to reduce computational costs so this is just the stem of a
이것은 단지 줄기 그래서 병목 계산 비용을 줄이기 위해
network and actually each of these parts is sort of different so they've got for
그들이 가지고 있도록 네트워크와 실제로 각이 부품은 종류의 다른
abuse inception modules been this but down sampling module then what seven of
남용 개시 모듈이되어 있지만 아래로 다음의 어떤​​ 일곱 모듈을 샘플링
these guys and then another down sampling module and then three more of
이 사람하고 다른 다운 샘플링 모듈과의 다음 3 개의
these guys and then finally they have dropped out and and fully connected lair
다음이 사람과 마침내 그들은 중퇴하고 완전히 은신처를 연결
for the class labels so another thing to point out is again there's no sort of
지적하는 또 다른 것은 그래서 클래스 레이블 다시의 어떤 종류가 없습니다
fully connected hitler's here they just have this global averaging to compute
완전히 연결 히틀러의 이곳은 단지 계산이 세계 평균이
the final feature vector and another cool thing they did in this paper was
마지막 특징 벡터 그들이 본 논문에서 한 또 다른 멋진 일이었다
inception residents so they propose this residual version of Inception
처음 거주자들은 셉션이 잔류 버전을 제안 할 수 있도록
architecture which is also pretty big and scary the stem is the same as before
또한 줄기 꽤 크고 무서운 아키텍처는 이전과 동일
and now these residues repeated inception blocks that they repeat
이제 이러한 잔기는 반복 개시 블록 반복
throughout the network they actually have these residual connections so
네트워크를 통해 그들은 실제로 이러한 잔류 연결 그래서이
that's that's kind of cool their kind of jumping on this residual idea
즉, 그 종류의이 잔류 생각에 점프의 그 종류를 냉각 것입니다
and now improved state of the art image not so again they have many repeated
지금하지 그래서 다시 그들은 많은 반복이있는 아트 이미지의 상태를 개선
modules and when you add this thing all up it's about 7875 layers assuming I did
모듈 및 모든 업이 일을 추가 할 때 내가했던 가정에 대한 7875 층의
the math right it last night so they also show that between their sort of new
수학은 바로 그렇게 그들은 또한 마지막 밤을 표시하는 새로운 자신의 종류의 사이
inception but their new version 4 of Inception Google Maps and their residual
처음하지만 인 셉션 Google지도 및 잔류의 새로운 버전 4
version of Google Maps that actually both of them perform about the same so
실제로 모두 동일한 대해 수행 구글지도 버전이므로
this is true top five air as a function of epochs on image now you can see that
지금 당신이 볼 수있는이 이미지에 신 (新) 시대의 함수로 진정한 상위 5 공기를하다
the inception network and read it actually is converging a bit faster but
발단 네트워크와 실제로 빠른 비트를 수렴 읽을 수는 있지만
over time both of them sort of conversation about the same value so
같은 값에 대한 일종의 대화 그들 모두에게 시간에 너무
that that's kind of interesting that's kind of cool another thing that's kind
그 가지 종류의 다른 일을 멋진 흥미로운의 종류 있다는
of interesting to point out is this this this the raw numbers on the x-axis here
지적 흥미로운이 문서는 여기에서 x 축에 원료 수있다
these are a pox on image now these things are being trained for a hundred
이들은 지금 이러한 일들이 백을 위해 훈련중인 이미지에 수두 있습니다
and sixty Pakistan image net so that's that's a lot of training time but that's
그리고 그건 육십 파키스탄 이미지 그물 그래서 그 훈련에 많은 시간이다하지만 그건
that's enough of current events and let's go back to our regularly scheduled
즉, 현재 이벤트의 충분과의 정기적으로 예약 된 우리로 돌아 가자
programming so today oh yeah question I don't know I think it might be in the
프로그래밍은 그래서 오늘 오, 그래 질문에 나는 그것이 될 것 같아요 모른다
paper but I didn't read it carefully and other questions on russia's might drop
종이 그러나 나는주의 깊게 읽어하지 않았고 러시아의 다른 질문에 드롭 수
out whether it's only in the last layer I'm not sure again I didn't read the
이 마지막 층에서만인지 잘 모르겠어요에서 다시 난을 읽어 보지 않았
paper to to carefully yet but it's the link is here you should check it out
종이에 조심스럽게 아직하지만 링크가 당신이 그것을 확인해야합니다 여기 있어요
ok so today we're going to talk about to sort of two other topics that are
확인 그래서 오늘 우리는 두 개의 다른 주제의 종류에 대해 얘기하는거야
considered common things and research these days so those are segmentation
그래서 그 생각 일반적인 것들과 연구 요즘 분할이다
which is this sort of classic computer vision topic and also this idea of
이는 고전적인 컴퓨터 비전 주제의이 종류도 이런 생각입니다
attention which i think is a really has been a really popular thing to work on
내가 생각하는주의는 정말로 일하기 정말 인기있는 일이있다한다
in deep mourning over the past year especially so first we're gonna talk
우리가 거​​ 얘기있어 특히 첫 있도록 지난 한 해 동안 깊은 애도의
about segmentation so you may have remembered this slide from a couple
분할에 대해 당신은 몇에서이 슬라이드를 기억했을 수 있도록
lectures ago we talked about object detection that was talking about
강의 전에 우리에 대해 얘기했다 물체 검출에 대해 이야기
different tasks that people work on computer vision and we spent a lot of
사람들이 컴퓨터 비전에서 일을하고 우리가 많이 소비 다른 작업
time in the class talking about classification and back in lecture we
수업 시간 강의에서 다시 분류에 대해 이야기하고 우리
talk about different models for
다른 모델에 대해 이야기
localisation and for object detection but today we're actually gonna focus on
현지화 및 물체 감지하지만 오늘 우리는에 실제로거야 초점을거야
this idea of segmentation that we skipped over last time in this previous
우리가 이전에 마지막으로 시간이 지남에 따라 생략 분할이 생각
lecture so within segmentation there's sort of two different some tasks that we
두 개의 서로 다른 일부 작업의 종류 거기에 분할 이내에 강의하는 우리
need to make that we need to define and people actually work on these things a
우리가 정의 할 필요가 사람들이 실제로 이런 일에 작동하는지 확인 필요
little bit separately the first task is this idea called semantic segmentation
조금 별도로 첫 번째 작업은 의미 분할이라는 생각이다
so here we take an end we have an input image and we have some pics number of
그래서 여기에 우리는 우리가 입력 영상이 끝을 가지고 우리의 일부 사진 번호가
classes things like buildings and trees and ground and cow and whatever kind of
어떤 종류의 건물과 나무와 지상 및 암소와 같은 종류의 것
semantic labels you want usually have some small fixed number of classes also
당신은 일반적으로 원하는 의미 라벨은 또한 클래스의 몇 가지 작은 고정 번호가
typically you'll have some background class for first things that don't fit
일반적으로는 적합하지 않다 최초의 것들에 대한 몇 가지 배경 클래스를해야합니다
into these classes and then the task is that we want to take as input an inch
이러한 클래스에 다음 작업은 우리가 입력 인치로 수행 할 것입니다
and then we want to label every pixel in that image with one of these semantic
그리고, 우리는 이러한 의미 중 하나를 사용하여 해당 이미지의 모든 픽셀에 라벨을 할
classes so here we have taken this input image of these three cows in the field
우리가 현장에서 이러한 세 소의이, 입력 화상을 촬영 한 여기에서 매우 클래스
and the ideal output is this image where instead of being RGB values we actually
그리고 이상적인 출력 대신 인 RGB 값이 이미지는 우리가 실제로
have one class label per pixel we can do this and other images and maybe segment
우리는 이것과 다른 이미지와 아마 세그먼트를 할 수있는 픽셀 당 하나의 클래스 레이블이
out the trees and the sky and the road the grass so this type of task is pretty
나무와 하늘과 도로에서 잔디 때문에 작업이 유형의 예쁜
cool I think it gives you sort of a higher level of understanding of what's
멋진 나는 당신에게 무엇의 이해의 높은 수준의 종류를 제공합니다 생각
going on in images compared to just putting a single label on the whole
단지 전체에 단일 레이블을 넣어 비교 이미지에서 진행
image and this is actually a very old problem in computer vision so this at
영상이 너무 이것 실제로 컴퓨터 비전에서 아주 오래 된 문제
that predates sort of the deep learning revolution so this figure actually comes
이 그림은 실제로 온다, 그래서 그 깊은 학습 혁명의 종류를 선행
from a computer vision paperbacks in 2007 that didn't use any deep learning
컴퓨터 비전은 2007 년 문고에서 그 어떤 깊은 학습을 사용하지 않은
at all people had other methods for this a couple years ago the other a task that
모든 사람에서 다른에게 몇 년 전에 작업을이 다른 방법을 가지고 그
people work on is this thing right so the thing to point out here is that this
사람들은이 일을 여기서 지적하는 것은이 때문이다 바로 그래서입니다 작업
thing is not aware of instances so here this this image actually house or four
일이이 이미지는 실제로이 집 또는 네 그래서 여기에 인스턴스를 인식하지 못합니다
cows there's actually three cows standing up and one cow kinda laying on
실제로 좀 누워 서 세 소와 한 소 소 거기
the grass taking a nap but here in this output it's not really clear how many
이 출력 여기에 낮잠 만 복용 잔디는 정말 분명하지 않다 얼마나 많은
cows there are these different cow is actually there pixels overlap so here in
소는 서로 다른 소가 픽셀 그래서 여기에 겹쳐 실제로있다
the outputs there is no notion that there are different cows
가 없다는 출력이 다른 소 있다는 것을
miss output we're just labeling every pixel so it's maybe not as informative
그것은 어쩌면 같은 정보를하지 그래서 우리가 모든 픽셀을 라벨링하고 출력을 그리워
as you might like and that could actually lead to some problems for some
당신이 좋아할 것하고 실제로 일부에 대한 몇 가지 문제가 발생할 수 있으므로
downstream applications so it's overcome this
그것은 이것을 극복 그래서 다운 스트림 응용 프로그램
people have also separately work on this nor problem called instant segmentation
사람들은 개별적으로 인스턴트 분할이라는이나 문제에 작동 한
this also sometimes gets called simultaneous detection and segmentation
이것은 또한 때때로 동시 탐지 및 분할 호출되는
so here's the problem is again somewhere to before we have some set of classes
그래서 여기에 문제는 우리가 클래스의 일부 세트가 이전에 어딘가에서 다시가요
that were trying to recognize and given an input image we want to output all
그 인식하려고 우리가 모든 출력을 원하는 입력 영상을 받았다
instances of those classes and for each instance we want segment out the pixels
이러한 클래스의 각 인스턴스에 대한 인스턴스 우리는 픽셀 밖으로 세그먼트를 원하는
that belong to that instance so here in this in this input image there are
그가이 입력 이미지 때문에 여기에 해당 인스턴스에 속하는
actually three different people there's the two parents and the kid and now in
지금의 두 부모와 아이 실제로 세 가지 다른 사람들이있다
the output we actually distinguish between those different people in the
우리가 실제로에서와 다른 사람들을 구분 출력
input image which which those three people are now shown in different colors
그 세 사람들이 지금 서로 다른 색으로 표시되는 입력 영상
indicate different instances and again for each of those instances we're going
다른 인스턴스를 표시하고 다시 해당 인스턴스 각각에 대해 우리는거야
to label all the pixels in the input image that belong to that instance so
해당 인스턴스에 속하는 입력 이미지의 모든 픽셀을 레이블을 너무
these two tasks of semantic segmentation and instant segmentation people actually
의미 분할 실제로 인스턴트 분할 사람들이 두 작업
have worked on them a little bit separately so first we're gonna talk
조금 별도로에서 일한 우리가 거​​ 얘기 야 처음 그래서
about some models for semantic segmentation so remember this is the
의미 론적 분할에 대한 일부 모델에 대해 그래서 이것은 기억
task for you want to just label all the pixels in the image and you don't care
당신을위한 작업은 이미지의 모든 픽셀에 레이블을 원하는 당신은 상관 없어
about instances so here the idea is actually pretty simple given some input
그래서 여기에 인스턴스에 대한 생각은 일부 입력 주어진 실제로 매우 간단하다
image this is the final in with the cows we're gonna take some little patch of
이미지 이것은 우리가거야 소와의 마지막은 일부 작은 패치를 가지고있다
the input image and extract this patch that sort of gives local information in
입력 이미지와는 종류의 현지 정보를 제공하는이 패치를 추출
image then we're gonna take this patch and we're gonna feed it through some
이미지는 우리는거야이 패치를 가지고 우리는 몇 가지를 통해거야 공급을거야
convolutional neural network this could be any of the architecture is that we've
콘벌 루션 신경망이 아키텍처 중 우리가된다는 것입니다 수
talked about so far in the class and now this
지금까지 클래스 이제이 이야기
convolutional neural network will actually classified the center pixel a
콘벌 루션 신경망 실제로 중심 화소 A를 분류 할
patch so this neural network is Justin classification that's something we know
패치 그래서이 신경 네트워크는 우리가 알고있는 뭔가 저스틴 분류입니다
how to do so this thing is just going to say that the center pixel of dispatch
그래서이 일을 그냥 말 것입니다 수행하는 방법이 파견의 중심 픽셀
actually is a cow than we can imagine taking this network that works on
실제로 우리가 작동이 네트워크를 복용 상상할 수있는 것보다 소입니다
patches
패치
and labels the center pixel and we just run it over the entire image and that
및 중앙 픽셀 레이블 그리고 우리는 단지 전체 이미지에 걸쳐 것을 실행
will give us a label for each pixel in the image so this actually is a very
이 실제로 매우 그래서 우리에게 이미지의 각 픽셀에 대한 레이블을 제공합니다
expensive operation right because now there's many many patches in the image
이제 이미지의 많은 많은 패치를 거기에 바로 있기 때문에 비용이 많이 드는 작업
and it would be super super expensive to run this network independently for all
그리고 그것은 모두 독립적으로이 네트워크를 실행하는 슈퍼 슈퍼 비싼 것
of them so in practice people use the same trick that we saw an object
그들의 연습 사람들이 우리가 물체를 보았다 같은 트릭을 사용 그렇게
detection where you'll run this thing fully convolutional II and get all the
완전히 길쌈 II를이 일을 실행하고거야 검출 모든
outputs for the whole image all at once but the problem here is that if you're
한 번에 전체 이미지 그러나 여기에서 문제에 대한 출력은 당신이 인 경우이다
convolutional network contains a kind of down sampling either to pooling or
컨볼 루션 네트워크 풀링에 또는 어느 샘플링 다운의 종류를 포함
through striker convolutions then now your output your output image will
다음 이제 출력 출력 이미지 것 스트라이커 회선을 통해
actually have a smaller spatial size and your input image so that's that's
그 그건 그래서 실제로 작은 공간 크기와 입력 이미지가
something that people need to work around when they're using this type of
그들은 이러한 유형의를 사용할 때 사람들이 주위에 일을해야 할 일
approach so any any questions on this kind of basic setup for semantic
접근의 의미에 대한 기본 설정의이 종류에 해당하므로, 어떠한 질문
segmentation yeah
분할 그래
the question is whether pat pat pat right thing just doesn't give you enough
문제는 팻 팻 팻 옳은 일을 그냥 충분히 제공하지 않습니다 여부
information in some cases and that's true so sometimes for these for these
어떤 경우에는 정보와 그 다음 이러한 위해 이렇게 때때로 진실
networks people actually have a separate offline refinement stage where they take
네트워크 사람들은 실제로 그들이 가지고 별도의 오프라인 정제 단계를
this output and then feed it to some kind of graphical model to clean up to
다음이 출력은 최대 청소 그래픽 모델의 일종으로 공급
clean up the output a little bed so sometimes that can help boost your
밀어 도움이 될 수 있도록 때때로 출력 조금 침대를 정리하여
performance a little better but justice for input-output model set up tents to
입력 - 출력 모델에 대한 좀 더 나은 성능을하지만 공의에 텐트를 설정
work pretty well just as something easy to implement yeah I'm you need I'm not
그냥 그래 난 당신이 아니에요 필요 해요 구현하기 쉬운 무언가로 꽤 잘 작동
sure I'm not sure exactly probably pretty big maybe a couple hundred 200
확실히 나는 정확히 아마 꽤 큰 어쩌면 몇 백 200 모르겠어요
pixels that order of magnitude so one extension that people have used to this
크기 때문에 하나의 확장의 순서로하는 사람들이 사용했다고하는 것이 픽셀
basic approach is this idea of multiscale testing actually sometimes a
기본적인 접근 방식은 실제로 때때로 다중 스케일 시험이 좋습니다
single scale isn't enough so here we're going to take our input image and will
단일 규모는 우리가 우리의 입력 이미지를 데리고가는 것하고 그래서 여기 충분하지 않습니다
actually resize it to multiple different sizes so this is sort of a common trick
이 공통 트릭의 일종이다, 그래서 실제로는 여러 다른 크기로 크기를 조정
that people use in computer vision a lot called an image pyramid you just take
사람들이 컴퓨터 비전에 사용하는 것이 많은 이미지 피라미드 방금 걸릴라고
the same dimension and you resize it made many different scales and now for
같은 차원과 당신은 지금 많은 다른 스케일을 만든 및 크기 조정
each of these scales were gonna run it through a convolutional neural network
이러한 비늘 각각은 컨볼 루션 신경망을 통해 실행 된 거
that is going to protect these pics are wise labels for these different images
그 다음 사진을 보호하는 것입니다 서로 다른 이미지의 현명한 라벨은
of these different resolutions so another thing to point out here along
이러한 서로 다른 해상도의 너무 다른 점은 여기에 따라 지적합니다
the lines of your question that if each of these networks actually has the same
질문의 라인이 각각의 네트워크가 실제로 동일한 경우 해당
architecture then each of these outputs will have a different effect of
아키텍처는 이러한 출력은 각각 다른 영향을 미칠 것입니다
receptive field in the input 2222 the image pyramid so now that we've gotten
그래서 지금 우리가 입수 한 것을 입력 2222 이미지 피라미드 수용 필드
these differently sized pixel labels for the intention than we can take all of
우리는 모두를 취할 수있는 것보다 의도에 대해이 다른 크기의 픽셀 라벨
them and Risa and just do some offline up sampling to up sample those responses
그들과 리사와 그냥 그 응답을 샘플링하는 일부 오프라인 업 샘플링을
to the same size as the input image so now we've gotten our three outputs of
그래서 지금 우리는 우리의 3 개의 출력을 쪘 입력 이미지와 동일한 크기로
different sizes up samples and stack them and this paper this actually paper
다른 샘플을 크기 및 그들과이 글이 실제로 종이를 쌓아
from the coon back in 2013 so they actually also have this separate
다시 2013 년 검둥이에서 그래서 그들은 실제로이 별도의이
off-line processing stap where they do this idea of a bottom-up segmentation
오프라인 처리 STAP 그들은 상향식 (bottom-up) 분할이 생각하는 곳
using right using these super pixel methods so these are these sort of more
이러한 이상이 일종의 그래서 이러한 슈퍼 픽셀 방법을 사용하여 권한을 사용하여
classic computer vision image processing type
고전 컴퓨터 비전 화상 처리 유형
methods that actually look at the differences between adjacent pixels and
실제로 인접 픽셀 사이의 차이를 보면 방법
images and then try to merge them together to give you these coherent
다음 둘을 병합하려고 이미지는 당신이 일관성을 제공합니다
regions where there are not much change in image so then this method actually
그럼 실제로이 방법 이미지에별로 변화가있는 지역
takes sort of runs the image offline through these other more traditional
소요 종류의 이러한 다른 전통적인을 통해 이미지를 오프라인으로 실행
image processing techniques to get either a set of super pixels or trees
이미지 처리 기술은 슈퍼 픽셀 또는 나무의 세트를 얻을 수
saying which pixels ought to be merged together in the image and they have this
화소 말은 이미지에 병합되어야한다 그리고 그들은이 있습니다
somewhat complicated process for merging all these different things together
이러한 모든 다른 일을 병합하는 다소 복잡한 과정
cause now we've gotten this sort of low-level information saying which
이제 우리는 낮은 수준의 정보 말 이런 종류의 쪘 유발하는
pixels in the image
이미지의 픽셀
actually are similar to each other based on sort of color and great information
실제로 색상과 좋은 정보의 종류에 따라 서로 유사하다
and we've got these outputs of different resolutions from the convolutional
우리는 길쌈에서 서로 다른 해상도의 이러한 출력을 가지고있어
neural networks telling us semantically what the labels are at different points
신경망 레이블이 다른 지점에있다 의미 무엇인지 우리에게 이야기
in the image and they use may actually explore a couple different ideas for
이미지에 그들은 실제로에 대한 몇 가지 아이디어를 탐구 할 수 사용
merging these things together to give you your final out what this actually
함께이 일을 합병하는 것은 당신에게 당신의 마지막을 어떻게이 사실은 알아주는
also answers when I addresses one of the earlier questions about the conflict not
나는 갈등에 대한 이전 질문 중 하나가 해결 될 때 또한 응답
being enough on its own so using these external read super pixel methods or the
그래서 이러한 외부 읽기 슈퍼 픽셀의 방법 또는를 사용하여 자체적으로 충분히있는
segmentation trees is another thing that sort of gives you additional information
분할 나무 종류의 당신에게 추가 정보를 제공하는 또 다른 일이
about maybe larger context in the input images so any any questions about this
입력 이미지에 대한 어쩌면 더 큰 문맥이 약하므로, 어떠한 질문
model ok so another another sort of cool idea that people have used for semantic
확인 모델을 다른 사람들이 의미에 사용되는 것을 멋진 아이디어를 다른 종류의 이렇게
segmentation in this is this idea of iterative refinement so we actually saw
이에 분할은 반복 정제의이 아이디어는 우리가 실제로보고있다
this a few lectures ago when we talked to many mentioned pose estimation but
우리가 얘기 할 때이 몇 강의 전에 언급 한 많은 추정을 제기하지만,
the idea is that we're gonna have an input image here they separated out the
아이디어는 우리가거야 그들이 밖으로 분리 여기에 입력 된 이미지를 가지고 있다는 것입니다
three channels and we're gonna run that thing for our favorite sort of
세 가지 채널 그리고 우리는 우리의 마음에 드는 종류에 대한 그 일 거 실행있어
convolutional neural network to predict these low resolution patches
콘벌 루션 신경망이 저해상도 패치를 예측할
rather to predict this no resolution segmentation of the image and now we're
오히려 이미지의이없는 해상도 분할을 예측하고 지금 우리는있어
gonna take that output from the CNN together with a Down sampled version of
거야의 다운 샘플링 된 버전과 함께 CNN에서 해당 출력을
the original image and we'll just repeat the process again so this allows the
우리가이 과정을 반복합니다 및 원본 이미지를 다시 때문에이 허용
network to sort of wine increase its effective receptive field of the output
네트워크는 출력의 유효 수용 필드를 증가 포도주를 정렬하려면
and also to perform or processing on the on the input image and then we can
또한 수행하거나 처리를의 입력 이미지를 그리고, 우리는 할 수있는
repeat this process again so this is kinda cool so if these three
이 좀 멋진 그래서 다시이 과정을 반복이 세 가지를 그렇다면
convolutional
길쌈
networks actually share weights then this becomes a recurrent convolutional
네트워크는 실제로 다음이 재발 길쌈가된다 가중치를 공유
network where it sort of operating on the same input over overthrew time but
네트워크 어디 종류의 전복 시간에 동일한 입력으로 작동하지만,
actually each of these updates steps is a whole convolutional network that's
실제로 이러한 업데이트 단계는 각각의 전체 컨벌루션 네트워크는
actually a very similar idea to recurrent networks that we saw
실제로 매우 유사한 아이디어는 우리가 본 네트워크를 재발하기
previously and the idea behind this paper which was in 2014 is that if you
이전에 2014 년에 있었던이 논문의 뒤에 아이디어는 것입니다 당신이 경우
actually do more iterations of the same type of thing then hopefully it allows
실제로는 수 잘하면 것은 동일한 유형의 더 많은 반복을 수행
the network to sort of iteratively refine its outputs so here if we have
네트워크는 일종의 반복적 그래서 여기에 우리가있는 경우 그 출력을 수정하기
this raw input image then after one generation you can see that actually
이 원시 입력 이미지는 한 세대 후에는 실제로 볼 수 있습니다
there's quite a bit of noise especially on the boundaries of the objects but as
특히 객체의 경계에 있지만 같은 소음이 꽤가있다
we run for two and three iterations through this recurrent convolutional
우리는이 재발 길쌈을 통해 둘, 셋, 반복에 대해 실행
network and actually allows the network to clean up a lot of that sort of
네트워크 실제로는 그런 종류의 많은 정리하기 위해 네트워크를 할 수 있습니다
low-level malaise and produced much cleaner much cleaner and nicer results
낮은 수준의 불쾌 및 생산 훨씬 청소기 훨씬 깨끗하고 더 멋진 결과
so I thought that was quite quite a cool idea that sort of merging together these
그래서 나는 함께 이러한 병합의 종류 아주 아주 멋진 아이디어라고 생각했다
idea of recurrent networks and sharing weights over time with this idea of
재발 네트워크의 아이디어와이 아이디어를 시간이 지남에 따라 가중치를 공유
convolutional networks to process images so another another very widely very well
컨볼 루션 네트워크는 아주 잘 매우 광범위하게 다른 그래서 이미지를 다른를 처리하는
very very well-known paper for semantic segmentation is this one from Berkeley
의미 론적 분할에 매우 매우 잘 알려진 논문은 버클리에서이 하나입니다
that was published at CBP our last year so here it's very similar model as
그는 CBP에 게시 된 우리의 지난해 그래서 여기에 그것은 매우 유사한 모델이다
before we're going to take an input image and run it through some number of
우리는 입력 영상을 가지고 어떤 수를 통해 실행하는거야 전에
convolutions and eventually extract some some feature map for the pixels but in
회선은 결국 화소하지만 일부 일부 기능지도를 추출
contrast the previous methods all rely on this sort of hard-coded up sampling
모든 하드 코딩 된 업 샘플링 이런 종류의에 의존하는 기존 방법 대비
to actually produce the final segmentation for the energy but in this
실제로 에너지하지만이에 최종 분할을 생산하는
paper they proposed that well we're we're deep learning people we want to
종이 그들은 잘 우리는 우리가 우리가 원하는 깊은 학습 사람들이야이야 제안
learn everything so we're gonna learn the upsampling as part of the network so
우리가 거​​ 네트워크의 일환으로 업 샘플링을 배울 수있는, 그래서 모든 것을 배울 그래서
they're not work includes this at the last layer this learnable up sampling
그들은없는 일이 마지막 층이 최대 학습 가능 샘플링에서이 포함되어있어
there that actually up samples the feature map in a learnable way so yes
이 실제로 최대 샘플 때문에 학습 가능 방식으로 기능지도 예
they have been up sampling map at the end and the way their model kind of
그들은 마지막에 샘플링지도와 길을 자신의 모델 종류까지왔다
looks is that they have this at the time it was an Alex not so they have their
그들은 그것을하지 그래서 그들은이 알렉스 된 시간에이를 것으로되어 보이는 그들의
input image running through many phases of convolution and pulling and
회선 및 당기 및 여러 단계의 실행 입력 영상
eventually they produce at this pool 5 output they have a quite
결국 그들은 그들이 가지고있는이 풀 (5) 출력에서​​ 생산 꽤
down sample image quite a Down sampled special size compared to the input image
샘플 이미지 아래 특별한 크기 샘플링 상당히 아래로 입력 화상과 비교하여
and then there are learnable up sampling reup them up samples that back to the
다음까지 학습 가능 샘플링이 다시에 샘플을 그들을 reup있다
original size of the input image
입력 화상의 원래 크기
another cool feature of this paper was this idea of skip connections so they
이 논문의 또 다른 멋진 기능은 스킵 연결이 아이디어들은 그렇게
actually don't use only just these poor five features they actually use the
그들은 실제로을 사용하여 실제로 단지이 가난한 오 기능을 사용하지 않는
convolutional features from different layers and the network which sort of
다른 레이어와 네트워크에서 길쌈 기능하는 일종의
exist at different scales so you can imagine that once you're in the pool for
당신이 상상할 수 있도록 다양한 규모에서 존재하는 당신의 수영장에있어 한 번
a layup Alex now that's actually a bigger feature map then the pool five
알렉스는 지금 실제로의 레이 업 후 더 큰 기능지도 풀 오
and pool 3 is even bigger than pool for so the intuition is that these lower
수영장 3 그래서 직관이 낮은 것입니다에 대한 풀보다 더 크다
convolutional airs might actually help you capture finer grain structure in the
길쌈 방송 해 실제로 당신이에 미세한 입자 구조를 캡처 도움이 될 수 있습니다
input image since they have a smaller receptive field so actually impact us
그들은 작은 수용 필드가 있기 때문에 입력 이미지가 그래서 실제로 우리에게 영향을
take these different convolutional feature maps and apply a separate
서로 다른 길쌈 기능 맵을 별도 적용
learned up sampling each of these feature maps and then combine them all
최대 배운 그들 모두를 결합 한 후이 기능 맵의 각을 샘플링하고
to produce the final output and in the result they show that actually adding he
최종 출력을 생성하고 그 결과에 그들은 실제로 그가를 추가하는 것을 보여
skipped connections tends to help a lot with these low-level details so over
스킵 연결을 통해 때문에 이러한 낮은 수준의 세부 사항에 많은 도움이 경향
here on the left these are the results that only use these poor five outputs
여기 왼쪽에있는 이들 만이 가난한 오 출력을 사용하는 결과는
and you can see that it's sort of gotten the rough idea of a person on a bicycle
당신은이 종류의 자전거에 사람의 거친 생각이라도 것을 알 수 있습니다
but it's kinda blobby and missing a lot of the fine details are on the edges but
하지만 좀 blobby 그리고 미세한 세부 사항을 많이 누락 가장자리에 있지만
then when you add in these steps connections from these lower
당신은 이러한 낮은에서 다음 단계 연결에 추가 할 때
convolutional errors that gives you a lot more fine-grained information about
당신에 대한 더 많은 세부적인 정보를 제공 길쌈 오류
the spatial locations of things in the image so that action so adding those
그 작업이 그렇게 사람들을 추가 있도록 이미지에서 사물의 공간 위치
skip connections in the lower layers really helps you clean up the boundaries
하위 계층에서 연결을 이동하는 것은 정말 경계를 정리하는 데 도움이
in some cases for these these outputs question so the question is how to
이 이러한 출력 질문에 대한 몇 가지 경우에 문제는 방법이다 있도록
classify accuracy I think the two metrics people typically used for this
정확성을 분류 나는 사람들이 일반적으로이 사용되는 두 메트릭 생각
are even just classification as you're classifying every pixel classification
당신이 모든 픽셀 분류를 분류하고 같이 다만 분류입니다
my tracks also sometimes people use intersection of a union so for each
내 트랙은 또한 때때로 사람들은 각각 그래서 노동 조합의 교차를 사용
class you compute what is the region of the image that I predicted us that class
클래스 당신은 내가 우리에게 그 클래스를 예측 이미지의 영역이 무엇인지 계산
and what was the reach the ground troops region of the image that had that class
이었다 무엇 클래스를 가지고 이미지의 지상군 영역에 도달
and then compute an intersection of a union between those two I'm not sure
다음 두 사이에 노동 조합의 교차점을 계산 나는 확실하지 않다
which which metric this paper used in particular
이는 측정하는 특히 사용이 논문
so this idea of learnable up sampling is actually really cool and since since
이렇게까지 ​​학습 가능 샘플링이 아이디어는 실제로 정말 멋진 이후부터입니다
this paper has been applied and a lot of other contacts cuz we know we've seen
이 문서가 적용되었습니다 및 기타 연락처를 많이는 우리가 본 적이 우리가 알고있는 사촌
that we can down sample our feature maps in a variety of different ways but being
우리는 아래로 우리의 기능지도를 다양한 방법으로뿐만되는 샘플 수 있음
able to up sample them inside the network could actually be very useful
최대 네트워크 내부를 샘플링 할 수 실제로 매우 유용 할 수있다
and a very valuable thing to do so this sometimes gets called deconvolution
매우 가치있는 일이 그래서이 때로는 호출되는 디컨 볼 루션을 수행하는
that's not a very good terms so we all talk about that in a couple minutes but
즉 우리 모두가 몇 분 안에 그 이야기 때문에 매우 좋은 조건은 아니지만
it's a very common term so just just to recap sort of when you're doing a normal
당신이 정상적인 일을 할 때 그냥 일종의 요약하자면, 그래서 그것은 매우 일반적인 용어이다
sort of stride stride 1353 convolution we we have this we have this picture
보폭 보폭 1353 컨볼 루션 우리의 종류 우리는 우리가이 사진을 가지고이 있습니다
that should be pretty familiar by now that given our four-by-four input we
즉 우리의 4 × 4 입력 우리를 부여하는 것이 지금까지 꽤 잘 알고 있어야합니다
have some three by three filter and we plot that three by three filter over
세 가지 필터에 의해 약 3를 가지고 우리는 이상이 셋으로 세 가지 필터를 플롯
part of the input
입력의 일부
product and that gives us one element of the output and now because the sting
제품이 우리에게 지금 고통 때문에 하나의 출력 요소 및 제공
asteroid one to compute the next element of the output we we moved the filter
아스테로이드 하나는 필터를 이동 출력 우리의 다음 요소를 계산
over one slot in the input again computer dot product and that gives us
하나의 입력을 다시 컴퓨터 내적의 슬롯을 통해 그 우리를 제공합니다
are one element in the output and now for stride true convolution it's it's a
출력에서 하나의 원소이며, 현재 걸음에 해당 회선에 대한 그것의 A의
very similar type of idea where now
아이디어의 매우 유사한 유형 어디
output is going to be a Down sampled version 2 by two output for a
출력은 두 개의 출력으로 버전이 샘플링 다운 될 것입니다
four-by-four in place and again it's the same idea we take our filter we plopped
4 × 4 곳에서 다시는 우리가 우리의 필터를 같은 생각 가지고있어 우리는 풍덩
down on the image computer dot product gives us one element of the output the
화상 컴퓨터 내적 아래로 우리에게 출력의 한 요소를 준다
only difference is that now we slide the convolutional filter over two slots and
유일한 차이점은 지금 우리가 두 개의 슬롯을 통해 컨볼 루션 필터를 밀어 것입니다
the input to compute one on into the outputs the deconvolution elaire
입력은 출력에 디컨 볼 루션 elaire 하나를 계산
actually does something a little bit different so here we want to take a low
실제로 우리가 저를 먹고 싶어 그래서 여기에 조금 다른 무언가를
resolution input and produce a higher resolution output so this would be maybe
해상도 입력하고 그래서 이것은 아마 것보다 높은 해상도 출력을 생성
a few by free deconvolution with a straight up to an appt at one so here
바로 그래서 여기에 하나에서 APPT까지의 무료 디컨 볼 루션에 의해 몇
this is a little bit weird you know in a normal convolution you imagine take you
이것은 당신이 정상적인 회선 알고있는 이상한 조금 당신을 상상하다
have your three by three filter and you take dot products and the input but here
당신의 세 가지로 세 개의 필터가 있고 여기에 도트 제품과 입력을하지만,
you want to imagine taking your three by three filter and just copying it over to
당신은 당신의 세 가지로 세 가지 필터를 복용 상상 할 단지에 이상 복사
the output the only difference is that the weights like this one scalar value
출력은 유일한 차이점은이 하나의 스칼라 값을 같은 무게
of the weight and your input
무게 및 입력
gives you a wait for that you're going to relate that filter when you stand
당신에 대한 대기를 제공합니다 당신은 당신이 설 때 필터를 관련 거라고
into the output and now when we started this thing along we're gonna step 1 step
우리가 거​​의 1 단계 발짝을 따라 우리가이 일을 시작했을 때 출력에 지금
over in the input and two steps over any output now we're going to take the same
모든 출력을 통해 이상 입력과 두 단계 이제 우리는 같은 걸릴거야
the same learned convolutional filter and we're gonna plopped down in the
우리는 동일한 학습 컨볼 루션 필터 아래로 풍덩거야
output but now in the boob now for taking the same convolutional filter and
같은 컨볼 루션 필터를 주셔서 지금은 가슴으로 출력하지만, 지금
we're popping it down twice in the output the difference being that the
우리는 차이가 있다는 것을 출력에 두 번을 보여주고있어
Redbox that convolutional filter is weighted by this scalar value in the
레드 박스는 컨볼 루션 필터는이 스칼라 값에 의해 가중된다
input and for the blue box that convolutional filter is weighted by the
입력과 파란색 상자에 대한 컨볼 루션 필터에 의해 가중된다
blue scalar value in the input and where these where these regions overlap you
블루 스칼라 입력의 값과 위치를이 곳이 지역이 당신을 중복
just add so this kind of allows you to learn and up sampling inside the network
바로이 종류의 당신이 배울 수 있으며 네트워크 내부 샘플링까지 이렇게 추가
so if you remember from your from implementing convolutions on the
그래서 당신은에 구현 회선에서에서 기억한다면
assignment this idea of sort of especially striking and adding an
할당 일종의 특히 눈에 띄는과 추가의이 아이디어
overlapping regions that should remind you of the backward pass for a normal
보통의 뒤로 패스 당신을 생각 나게한다 겹치는 영역
convolution and it turns out that these are completely equivalent that this
회선 및 이들이 그 완전히 동일하다는 것을 밝혀
deconvolution forward pass is exactly the same as the normal convolution
컨벌루션 포워드 패스 정확하게 정상 컨벌루션와 동일
backward pass and the normal and the deconvolution backward pass is the same
역방향 패스 정상 및 컨벌루션 후방 패스는 동일
as the normal convolution forward pass so because of that actually the term
일반 회선 앞으로 때문에 실제로 용어는 그렇게 통과
deconvolution is maybe not so great and if you have a signal processing
디컨 볼 루션 어쩌면 그렇게 크지 않다 당신은 신호 처리가있는 경우
background you may have seen that deconvolution already has a very
당신이 디컨 볼 루션 이미 본 적이있다 배경은 매우가
well-defined meaning and that is the inverse of convolution so a
의미는 잘 정의하고 그 때문에 회선의 역입니다
deconvolution should undo a convolution operation which is quite different from
디콘 볼 루션은 상당히 다르다 컨벌루션 연산을 취소해야
what this is actually doing so probably better names for this instead of
어떤이 실제로 그렇게하는 대신 이에 대한 아마 더 좋은 이름을하고있다
deconvolution that you'll sometimes see will be convolution transpose or our
가끔 볼 수 디컨 볼 루션은 컨볼 루션 전치 또는 우리가 될 것
backwards strident convolution or fractionally strident convolution or or
뒤로 귀에 거슬리는 회선 또는 단편적으로 귀에 거슬리는 회선 또는 또는
up convolution so I think those are kind of weird names I think deconvolution as
나는 이러한 종류의 이상한 이름이라고 생각하므로 회선까지 나는대로 디컨 볼 루션을 생각한다
popular just cuz it's easiest to say even though it may be less technical
인기가 덜 기술 될 수있다하더라도 말을 쉬운 그냥 사촌
technically correct although actually if you read papers you'll see that some
당신이 논문을 읽고 실제로 경우 그 일부를 볼 수 있지만 기술적으로 정확
people get angry about this so
사람들은 그래서 이것에 대해 화
it's more proper to say convolution transpose instead of deconvolution and
이 회선 대신 디컨 볼 루션의 트랜스 말을 더 적절한이고
this other paper really wants it to be colored fractionally stride convolution
이 다른 논문은 정말 분별 보폭 회선을 착색하고 싶어
so I think I think the community is still deciding on the right terminology
그래서 내가 사회는 여전히 올바른 용어를 결정할 생각 생각
here but I kind of agree with them the deconvolution is probably not very
여기 그러나 나는 이러한 종류의 디컨 볼 루션은 아마 매우 아니다 그들에 동의
technically correct and this this paper in particular has alcohol they felt very
기술적으로 정확하고 매우 느낌이 특히이 논문은이 알코올
strongly about this issue and they had a one-page index appendix to the paper
강하게이 문제에 대해 그들은 용지에 한 페이지 인덱스 부록했다
actually explaining why so I convolution transposase the proper term so if you're
당신이있어 그래서 만약 내가 적절한 용어를 트랜스 회선 왜 실제로 설명
interested then I would really recommend checking out that it's a pretty good
관심은 정말 꽤 좋은 것을 확인하는 것이 좋습니다 것입니다
explanation actually so any any questions about this
이에 대한 설명은 실제로 해당하므로, 어떠한 질문
yeah I think so the question is how much faster is this relative to a patch based
그래, 정말 문제는 패치이 상대를 기반으로 얼마나 빨리 생각
thing the answer is that in practice nobody even thanks to run this thing and
일이 대답은 연습 아무도에도 덕분에이 일을 실행하는 것입니다
hopefully patch beast mode that would just be way way too slow so actually all
단지 방법이 너무 느린 그래서 실제로 모든 것 희망 패치 짐승 모드
of the papers that i've seen
내가 본 논문의
do some kind of polly convolutional thing in one way or another
이럭저럭 폴리 길쌈 것은 어떤 종류의 작업을 수행
actually there there is sort of another trick instead of up sampling that people
실제로 다른 트릭의 대신 샘플링까지 종류가있다 그 사람
sometimes use and that is that so suppose that your network is actually
때때로 사용하고 그 때문에 네트워크가 실제로 있다고 가정이다
gonna down sample by a factor of four then one thing you can do is take your
4 배에 의해 거 아래 샘플은 당신이 할 수있는 한 가지 가지고 당신의
input image shipped by one pixel and now running through the network again and I
입력 이미지는 하나의 픽셀로 배송 지금은 다시 내가 네트워크를 통해 실행
you get another output and you repeat this for sort of four different one
다른 출력을 얻을 당신은 네 가지 일의 종류에 대해이 작업을 반복
pixel ships of the input and now you've gotten for output maps and you can sort
픽셀 입력의 선박 지금은 출력지도를받은 적이 당신은 정렬 할 수 있습니다
of interleaved those to reconstruct an original input map so that's that's
그 그건 그래서의 원래의 입력 맵을 재구성하는 인터리브
another trick that people sometimes used to get around that problem but I think
사람들이 가끔 사용되는 또 다른 트릭은 그 문제를 해결 얻을 수 있지만, 나는 생각한다
that this morning up sampling is quite a bit cleaner
오늘 아침 샘플링이 꽤 청소기입니다
so i think is really nice just rolls off the tongue I think back once tried I
그래서 내가 정말 좋은 나는 다시 한 번 I 시도라고 생각 혀를 롤 생각
think fractionally strident convolution is actually pretty cool right I think
단편적으로 귀에 거슬리는 회선 실제로 내가 생각하는 정말 멋진 권리라고 생각합니다
it's the longest name but it's really descriptive right normal with Astro
그것은 가장 긴 이름이다하지만 천체 정상 바로 정말 설명이다
normally with us try to convolution you move acts elements in the end he moved
일반적으로 우리와 그가 이동 결국 요소의 역할을 이동할 회선에 시도
like you don't want any input and output and here you're moving what happened the
같은 당신은 어떤 입력과 출력을하지 않으 여기에 당신은 무슨 일이 있었는지 이동하고
input you might wanna input which corresponds moving what happened the
무슨 일이 있었는지 움직이는 해당하는 입력하면 입력 싶어 있습니다
output so that captures idea quite nicely so I'm not sure what I'll call it
출력은 그래서 내가 내가 전화 할게 무엇인지 확실하지 않다, 그래서 아주 능숙하게 아이디어를 캡처
when when I use it in the paper we'll have to see about that but so despite
나는 신문에서 그것을 사용할 때 우리는 그것에 대해 그러나 지금에도 불구하고 참조해야 할 때
the despite the concerns about people calling a deconvolution like people just
사람들이 같은 디컨 볼 루션을 호출하는 사람들에 대한 우려에도 불구하고 단지
call it that anyway so there was this paper from ICC be that takes this idea
ICC에서이 논문은 수 있었다 어쨌든 그래서이 아이디어를 소요 호출
of this week of this convolutional / fractionally try to come up with an idea
이 길쌈의 금주의 / 단편적으로 생각을 마련하려고
and sort of pushed to the extreme so here and they they took what amounts to
그리고 일종의 그래서 여기에 극단적으로 푸시하고 ​​그들이 금액 무엇을했다
two entire BGG networks so this is an exact same models before I wanna input
이 전체 BGG 네트워크 I 입력 싶어하기 전에이는 동일한 모델 그래서
and output pixel wise predictions for the semantic segmentation task but here
의미 분할 작업하지만 여기 출력 픽셀 현명한 예측
we initialize the BGG and over here is an upside down BGG and it trains for six
우리는 BGG를 초기화 이상 여기 BGG 거꾸로이며, 그것은 육에 대한 훈련
days on a tax so this thing is pretty slow but actually got really really good
세금에 일 때문에이 일을 꽤 느린 실제로 정말 정말 좋은있어
results and I think it's also a very beautiful figure so that's that's pretty
결과와 나는 그 꽤 있어요 그래서 그것도 아주 아름다운 그림이라고 생각
much all that I have to say about semantic segmentation if there's any
많은 모든 내가 어떤 존재인지 의미 론적 분할에 대해 말할 필요가 있음
questions about that yeah
그에 대한 질문이 그래
the question is how is this your main the answer is I took a screenshot from
문제는 내가에서 스크린 샷을했다이 메인 답변입니다 방법입니다
their paper so I don't know but you can try to answer flow we saw in the last
자신의 종이 그래서 난 몰라하지만 당신은 우리가 마지막에서 본 흐름 답변을 시도 할 수 있습니다
lecture that lets you make make figures but they're not as nice as this yeah
그래 당신이 그림을 만들하지만이만큼 좋은 아니에요 수 있습니다 강연
question as training data yes there exists datasets with this kind of thing
훈련 데이터와 같은 질문은 예이 것은 이런 종류의 데이터 세트를 존재
where I think there's a common one is the Pascal segmentation data set so it
어디 파스칼 분할 데이터가 그렇게 설정되어 일반적인 일이 있다고 생각
just has a ground truth you have an image you have an image and they have
당신이 이미지가 접지 진실은 당신은 이미지를 그들은 가지고있다
every pixel labeled yeah it's it's kind of expensive to get that data to the
표시된 모든 픽셀 그래 그것은이 해당 데이터를 가져 가지 비싼이다
datasets tend to be a little smaller but in practice there's a famous interface
데이터 세트는 약간 작은 경향이 있지만, 실제로 유명한 인터페이스가있다
called label me where you could upload an image and then sort of drunk on tour
이미지를 업로드 할 수있는 곳 나 라벨을 불러 투어 다음 종류의 술
around the invention around different regions of the invention and that you
본 발명의 다른 지역의 주위에 당신이 본 발명의 주위에
can convert those contours into sort of these segmentation asks that's how you
이 세그먼트의 일종으로 그 윤곽을 변환 할 수 있습니다 묻는 그 방법을의
tend to label these things in a way if you are questions that I think we'll
당신은 우리가 거​​ 생각 질문이있는 경우 방식으로이 일에 라벨을하는 경향이
move on to instant segmentation so just to recap instance segmentation is this
다만 인스턴스 분할을 정리해 할 수 있도록이가 즉시 분할로 이동
generalization or where we not only want to label the pixels of the image but we
일반화 또는 우리뿐만 아니라 이미지의 픽셀에 라벨을 원하는 위치에 있지만
also want to distinguish instant distinguish instances so we're going to
또한 즉시 우리가가는거야 그래서 인스턴스를 구별 구별 할
detect the different instances of our classes and for each one we want to
우리 클래스의 다른 인스턴스를 감지하고 각각에 대해 우리가 원하는
label the pixels of that instance so these this actually these models and up
그래서이이 실제로이 모델 최대 인스턴스의 픽셀을 라벨
looking a lot like the detection models that we talked about a few lectures ago
우리가 전에 몇 강의에 대해 이야기 검출 모델처럼 많이 찾고
so one of the earliest papers that I know that this is actually I should also
그래서이 실제로 나는 또한해야 것을 알고 최초의 논문 중 하나
point out that this is i think im much more recent ask that this idea of
이 내가 메신저 훨씬 더 최근이의이 아이디어 부탁 생각이라고 지적
semantic segmentation has been used in computer vision for a long long time but
의미 론적 분할 긴 장시간 컴퓨터 비전에 사용되었지만
I think this idea of instant segmentation has gotten a lot more
나는 즉시 분할이 생각보다 많이받은 것 같아요
popular especially in the last couple of years so this paper from 2014 sort of
특히 2014 종류의에서이 논문 그래서 지난 몇 년에 인기
took this I think they call it simultaneous detection and segmentation
이 걸렸다 나는 그들이 그것을 동시 탐지 및 세분화를 호출 생각
or SDS that's kind of a nice name and this is actually very similar to our CNN
또는 SDS는 좋은 이름의 종류 그리고이 사실은 우리의 CNN과 매우 유사
model that we saw protection so here we're gonna take it and input dementia
우리가 여기에 보호를 보았다 모델은 우리가 입력 치매를 거 가지고있어
and if you remember in our CNN we rely on these external region proposals that
당신이 우리의 CNN에서 기억한다면 우리는 이러한 외부 지역의 제안에 의존하는
can are these sort of offline computer vision
오프라인 컴퓨터 비전의 이러한 종류입니다 수 있습니다
global thing that compute predictions on where it thinks objects in image might
이 이미지의 개체를 생각하는 위치에 예측을 계산 글로벌 일 수도
be located
위치
well it turns out that there's other methods for proposing segments instead
잘은 대신 세그먼트를 제안하기위한 다른 방법이 있다고 밝혀
of boxes so we just download one of those existing segment proposal methods
상자의 우리는 이러한 기존 세그먼트 제안 방법 중 하나를 다운로드
and use that instead now for each of these segments we can for each of these
이들 각각에 대해이 세그먼트 우리가 할 수있는 각 대신 지금 사용
proposed segments we can extract a bounding box by just sitting at a box of
제안 된 세그먼트 우리는 단지의 상자에 앉아하여 경계 상자를 추출 할 수 있습니다
a segment and then run crop out that chunk of the input image and run it
다음 세그먼트는 입력 영상의 덩어리에서 작물을 실행하고 실행
through a box CNN to extract features for that box than in parallel will run
상자를 통해 CNN이 실행됩니다 병렬보다 그 상자 기능을 추출
through a region CNN so she can we take that relevant that chunk from input
지역 CNN을 통해 그래서 그녀는 우리가 취할 수 입력에서 관련 청크
invention and crop it out but here because we actually have this proposal
발명 작물이 밖으로 그러나 여기에서 우리는 실제로이 제안을 가지고 있기 때문에
for the segment then we're going to mask out the background region using the mean
다음 세그먼트에 대해 우리는 평균을 사용하여 배경 영역을 마스크거야
color of the data that so this is kind of a hack that lets you take these kind
그래서 이것은 당신이이 종류를 취할 수있는 해킹의 일종이다 데이터의 색
of weird shape inputs and feed it into a CNN you just mask out the background
이상한 모양의 입력과 CNN로 먹이를 그냥 배경을 마스크
part with us with a black color so that may take these masks inputs and run them
검은 색으로 우리와 부분 그래서이 마스크 입력을하고 실행할 수 있습니다
through a separate regions CNN now we've gotten two different feature vectors one
별도의 영역을 통해 CNN은 지금 우리가 입수 한 두 개의 서로 다른 특징 벡터 하나
sort of incorporating the whole box and one in corporate only the of the
전체 상자를 통합의 종류 만 기업에서 하나의
proposed foreground pixels we concatenate these things and then just
제안 된 전경 픽셀 우리는 이러한 것들과 연결하여 바로
like in our CNN we make a classification to decide what class actually should
우리의 CNN에 우리가 구분을 같은 결정하는 어떤 클래스 실제로해야
this segment B and then they also have this region refinement step where we
이 세그먼트 B는 다음 그들은 또한이 지역의 정제 단계가 어디
want to refine the proposed regions the little bit so if you don't know how well
당신이 모르는, 그래서 만약 잘하는 방법을 제안 영역에게 조금 수정하려면
you remember that our CNN framework but this is actually very similar to our CNN
당신은 우리의 CNN 프레임 워크 기억하지만 실제로 우리의 CNN과 매우 유사
just apply to this instance simultaneous detection and segmentation task so this
다만이 경우 동시 검출 및 분할 작업 때문에이를 적용
idea for this region refinement step there's actually a follow-up paper that
이 지역의 정제 단계에 대한 아이디어는 실제로 후속 종이있다 그
proposes a pretty nice way to do it so here is the paper from the same folks at
같은 사람의 논문에서 이렇게 여기에서 그것을 할 수있는 아주 좋은 방법입니다 제안
berkeley though the following conference and here we want to take this this input
우리는이 입력을 할 버클리 다음 회의 있지만 여기
which is this proposed to segment this proposed segment and want to clean it up
이 세그먼트에 제안 된 세그먼트를 제안하고 그것을 정리할되는
somehow so we're actually gonna take a very similar approach very similar type
어떻게 든 우리는 실제로 매우 유사한 유형 매우 유사한 접근 방식을거야
multiscale approach that we saw in the
우리가에서 본 다중 스케일 방법
in the semantic segmentation model a while ago so here we're going to take
그래서 여기에 얼마 전 의미 분할 모델에서 우리는 걸릴거야
our our image crop out the prop up the box corresponding to that segment and
우리의 우리의 이미지 자르기 아웃이 해당 세그먼트에 해당하는 상자를 지탱하고
then pass it through and Alex net and we're going to extract convolutional
다음과 알렉스 그물을 통해 그것을 통과하고 우리는 길쌈을 추출 할거야
features from several different layers of that Alex NAT for each of those
그 각각에 대해 그 알렉스 NAT의 여러 레이어의 기능
feature maps will up sampled I'm and combine them together and now will
기능 맵은 최대 난과 함께 결합 지금 것 샘플링합니다
produce this this figure this proposed figure ground segmentation so this this
이이 그림이 제안 그림 지상 분할을 생성하므로이이
is actually kind of a funny output but it's it's really easy to predict the
가지 재미 출력 사실이지만 그것은 예측을 정말 쉽게있어
idea is that invests this output image we're just gonna do a logistic
아이디어는 우리가 단지거야이 출력 이미지가 물류를 수행 투자입니다
classifier inside each independent pixel so given these features we just have a
각각의 독립적 인 픽셀 내부 분류 그래서 우리는 단지이 이러한 기능을 제공
whole bunch of independent logistic classify hairs that are predicting how
독립 물류의 전체 무리를 어떻게 예측하고 머리카락을 분류
much each pixel of this output is likely to be in the foreground are in the
출력이 많은 화소가 전경 될 가능성이있다
background and they show that this this type of multiscale refinement step
배경과 그들이 보여이 다중 스케일 정제 단계의이 유형이
actually cleans up the other parts of the previous system and gives quite
실제로 이전 시스템의 다른 부분을 정리 아주 준다
quite nice results question
아주 좋은 결과 질문
fractionally stride and convolution I think it was instead of some kind of a
단편적으로 보폭 및 회선 나는 그것이 어떤 종류의 대신 생각
fix up sampling like a bilinear interpolation or something like that or
그 또는 같은 선형 보간 또는 뭔가처럼 샘플링을 수정
maybe even a nearest-neighbor just something fixed and variable but I could
어쩌면 가장 가까운 이웃 뭔가 고정 및 가변 그러나 나는 할 수
be wrong but you could definitely imagine swapping and some learnable
잘못하지만 당신은 확실히 교환 및 일부 학습 가능 상상할 수
think they're too
너무 것 같아요
ok so this this this actually is very similar to our CNN but in the detection
확인 그래서 실제로이이 우리의 CNN뿐만 검출에 매우 유사합니다
lecture we saw that our CNN was just the start of the story there's all these
우리는 우리의 CNN이 이야기의 시작에 불과했다 모든이 있다고 보았다 강의
faster versions right so it turns out that a similar intuition from faster our
그것이 나오는 바로 있도록 빠른 버전이 빠르게에서 유사한 직관 우리
CNN has actually been applied to this instance segmentation problem as well so
CNN은 실제로도 있으므로이 경우 세그멘테이션 문제에 적용된
this is work from Microsoft that action and this model actually won the cocoa
이 해당 작업이 모델은 실제로 코코아 우승 Microsoft에서 작품입니다
instance segmentation challenge this year so they they took their giant
예를 세분화 도전 그들의 거대한했다 그들은 그래서 올해
resonance and they stuck this model on top of it and they and they crush
공명 그들은 그 위에이 모델을 고집하고 그들은 호감
everyone else in the coco instance segmentation challenge so this this
코코 인스턴스 분할 도전에 다른 사람 때문에이이
actually is very similar to past our stand on so we're going to take our
실제로 우리가 걸릴 거 야에 우리의 독립 과거와 매우 유사하다 우리
input image and just like in fast and faster our CNN our input image will not
입력 영상 단지 빠른처럼 빠르게 우리의 CNN 우리의 입력 영상은하지 않습니다
be pretty high resolution and we'll get this giant comedy show will feature map
꽤 높은 해상도를하고 우리는이 거대한 코미디 쇼가지도 기능을합니다거야
over our high resolution and then from this high resolution and we're actually
우리의 높은 해상도를 통해 다음이 고해상도에서 우리는 실제로있어
going to propose our own region proposals in the previous method we
이전의 방법은 우리가 우리 자신의 영역 제안을 제안하는 것
relied on these external segment proposals but here we're just gonna
이러한 외부 세그먼트의 제안에 의존하지만, 여기에 우리는거야
learn our own region proposals just like faster our CNN so here we just stick a
우리는 그냥 막대기 우리 자신의 영역 제안이 너무 여기에 빠른 우리의 CNN을 좋아하는 배우
couple a couple extra convolutional airs on top up are controversial feature map
몇 가지 추가 길쌈 상단까지에 개최 부부는 논란 기능지도입니다
and each one of those is going to predict several regions of interest in
그 중 각 하나에 대한 관심의 여러 지역을 예측하는 것입니다
the image that using this idea of boxes that we saw in the detection work
이미지 우리가 검출 작업에서 본 상자의이 아이디어를 사용하여
the difference is that now once we have this region these region proposals were
차이점은 우리는이 지역이 지금은 일단이 지역의 제안이 있었다이다
gonna segment about using a very similar approach that we just saw on the last
우리가 마지막에 본 매우 유사한 접근 방식을 사용하는 방법에 대한 거 세그먼트
slide so for each of these proposed regions are going to use this ROI what
이 제안 된 영역 각각에 대해 너무 미끄러이 투자 수익 (ROI)을 사용하려고 무엇을
they call it ROI warping or pooling and squish them all down to a fixed square
그들은 뒤틀림이나 풀링 및 고정 된 사각형에 이르기까지 그들 모두를 뭉개 버려 ROI를 호출
size and then run each of them through a convolutional neural network to produce
크기하고 생성하는 컨볼 루션 신경망을 통해 각각 실행될
these course figure ground segmentation masks like we just saw in the previous
우리와 같은 이러한 과정 그림 지상 분할 마스크는 이전에보고
in the previous slide so now at this point we've gotten our image we've got a
이 시점에서 이제 이전 슬라이드에서 우리는 우리가 가지고 우리의 이미지를 쪘
bunch of region proposals and now for each region proposal we have a rough
각 지역의 제안에 대한 지역 제안의 무리 지금 우리는 거친이
idea of which part of that box as foreground and which part is background
전경 어느 한 부분으로 그 상자의 어느 부분의 아이디어는 배경입니다
now we're going to take this idea of masking so now that we predicted the
지금 우리는 우리가 예측하는 것이 지금 마스킹의 이런 생각을하는거야
foreground background for each of these segments we're going to mask out the
우리가 밖으로 마스크거야이 세그먼트의 각 전경 배경
predicted background and only keep the pixels from the predicted foreground and
배경을 예측 만 예측 전경에서 픽셀을 유지하고
past goes through another couple layers to actually classified about classify
과거 다른 몇 층을 통과 실제로 분류에 대한 분류하기
that segment as our different categories so this is a man this entire thing can
우리의 서로 다른 범주로 그 세그먼트 그래서이이 모든 일을 할 수있는 사람이다
just be learned jointly and two and with the idea that we've got these three
단지 공동으로 두 배울 수 및 아이디어 우리는이 세 가지 있는데 그
semantically interpretable outputs in intermediate layers of our network and
우리의 네트워크의 중간 계층에 의미 해석 출력 및
each of them we can just supervise with ground truth data so these regions of
그들 각각 우리는 그냥 그렇게이 지역 지상 진실 데이터를 감독 할 수 있습니다
interest we know where the ground truth sex objects are in the object and image
지상 진실 섹스 객체는 객체와 이미지에 어디에 관심을 우리는 알고있다
so we can provide supervision on those outputs for these segmentation asks we
이러한 분할이 우리 요청에 대해 우리는 그 출력에 감독을 제공 할 수 있습니다
know what the true foreground and background ours we can give supervision
우리가 감독을 줄 수있는 진정한 전경과 배경 우리 알고
there and we are we obviously know the classes of those different segments so
그리고 우리는 우리가 분명히 그렇게 그 다른 세그먼트의 클래스를 알고있다
we just provide supervision at different layers of these network and try to trade
우리는 이러한 네트워크의 여러 계층에서 감독을 제공하고 거래를하려고
off all those different lost terms and hopefully get the thing to converge but
모든 다른 손실 조건 해제와 희망을 수렴 할 수있는 일을 얻을 수 있지만,
this actually was trained and two and and they find to an interesting and it
이 실제로 훈련, 둘, 그들은 재미 있고 그것을에 발견되었다
works really really well so here is that the results figure that we have to show
정말 정말 잘 그래서 여기에 작동하는 결과가 우리가 보여해야한다는 그림이다
so these results are at least to me really really impressive so for example
그래서 이러한 결과는 정말 나에게 적어도 예를 들어, 그래서 정말 인상적이다
this input image has all these different people sitting in this room and the
이 입력 영상이 방에와 앉아이 모든 다른 사람들이
predicted outputs do a really good job of separating out all those different
예상 출력은 모든 다른를 분리하는 정말 좋은 일을
people even though they overlap and there's a lot of them and they're very
사람들은 중복에도 불구하고 많은있다 그리고 그들은 매우있어
close
닫기
same with these cars made it a little easier but especially this this people
이 차와 같은 조금 더 쉽게하지만, 특히이이 백성 만든
when I was pretty impressed by but you can see it's not perfect so this potted
나는 꽤 감동하지만, 때 당신은 그래서이 화분 완벽 하진 볼 수 있습니다
plants at that was blocked here than it really was and it confused this chair on
그에서 식물은 정말보다 여기 차단 그것은에이 의자를 혼동했다
the right for a person and I missed a person there but overall these results
사람에 대한 권리와 나는이 사람을 놓친하지만 전체 결과
are very very impressive and like I said this model one that Coco segmentation
아주 아주 인상적과 같은 나는이 모델 하나는 코코 세분화했다
challenge this year so the overview of segmentation is that we've got these
분할의 개요 우리가 이것들을 가지고 있다는 것입니다, 그래서 올해에 도전
these two different tasks semantic segmentation and instant segmentation
이 두 가지 작업 론적 분할 및 분할 인스턴트
for semantic segmentation it's very common to use this this
의미 분할을 위해이 이것을 사용하는 것은 매우 흔한 일
conde convoy approached and then for instance segmentation you end up with
콘데 호송은 접근 한 다음 예를 세분화 당신이와 끝까지
these pipelines that look more similar to object detection so if there's any
어떤이의 경우, 그래서 더 유사 이러한 파이프 라인 검출 객체하기
last minute questions about segmentation I can try to answer those now super
분할에 대한 마지막 순간의 질문에 나는 슈퍼 지금 그 대답을 시도 할 수 있습니다
clear I guess so we're gonna move on to another and are not a pretty cool
분명 나는 우리가 서로에 거 이동을하고있어 꽤 멋진 아닌 것 같아요
exciting topic and thats attention models so this is something that I think
흥미로운 항목이 너무 먹으 렴주의 모델은 내가 생각하는 뭔가
has got a lot of attention and last year and community so as a kind of a case
그래서 경우의 일종으로 관심과 작년과 지역 사회를 많이 가지고있다
study we're gonna talk about the model from another citation here ok but as a
연구 우리는 여기에서 확인하지만 같은 다른 인용문에서 모델에 대한 거 얘기 야
as a as a sort of a case study
사례 연구의 일종으로 같은
we're going to talk about the idea of attention as applied to image capture me
이미지에 적용되는 우리는 저를 캡처 관심의 아이디어에 대해 이야기하는거야
so I think this model was previewed in the recurrent networks lecture but we
그래서 나는이 모델이 재발 네트워크 강좌에 미리 있었다라고 생각하지만
want I want to step into a lot more details here but first as a recap just
나는 정리 해보 여기하지만 먼저 더 많은 세부 사항으로 단계하고자 원하는 단지
so we're on the same page hopefully you know how I missed captioning works by
그래서 우리는 희망 당신은 내가하여 자막 작업을 놓친 방법을 알고 같은 페이지에있어
now since the homework is due in a few hours but we're going to take our input
이제 숙제 때문에 몇 시간 예정이다 그러나 우리는 우리의 입력을거야
invention and run it through a convolutional not and get some features
본 발명은하고 길쌈을 통해 그것을하지 실행하고 일부 기능을 얻을
those features will be used maybe to initialize the first hidden state of our
이러한 기능의 첫 번째 숨겨진 상태를 초기화 아마 사용됩니다 우리
current network then are far start token or a first word got out that hidden
현재의 네트워크는 토큰 시작 멀리하거나 첫 번째 단어가 숨겨져 있음을 얻었다
state we're going to produce this distribution over words in our
상태는 우리가 단어 이상이 분포를 생성하는거야 우리
vocabulary than to generate a word will just simple format distribution and will
어휘 것입니다 단순한 형식으로 배포 단어를 생성하는 것보다 및 것
just sort of repeat this process overtime to generate captions the
그저 자막를 생성하기 위해이 프로세스 초과 근무를 반복
problem here is that this network only sort of gets one chance to look at the
여기서 문제는이 네트워크는 일종의 보는 하나의 기회를 얻을 수 있다는 것입니다
input image and when it does it's looking at the entire input image all at
입력 이미지와 그것이 전체 입력 영상에 모두를 찾고 않을 때
once and it might be cooler if it actually have the ability to one look at
실제로 한번보고하는 기능에있는 경우 한 번 그리고 냉각기 수 있습니다
the input image multiple times and also if it could focus on different parts of
그것이 다른 부분에 초점을 맞출 수 있다면, 또한 입력 화상 여러번
the input image as it ran so one pretty cool paper that came out last year was
작년에 나온 입력 이미지가 달렸다 정도로 하나의 정말 멋진 종이이었다
this one called show attendant tell the original one show and tell us they added
이 하나라는 쇼 교환은 원래 하나의 쇼를 말해 우리는 추가 말
the a-ten part and the idea is is pretty straightforward so we're going to take
ㄱ - 열 부분과 아이디어는 우리가 걸릴 거 야, 그래서 매우 간단합니다
our input image and we're still gonna run it through a convolutional network
우리의 입력 영상 그리고 우리는 여전히 컨볼 루션 네트워크를 통해 실행거야
but instead of extracting the features from the last fully connected later
대신 마지막 완전히 연결 이후의 특징을 추출
instead we're gonna pull features from one of the convoluted earlier
대신 우리는 이전 선상 중 하나에서 거 풀 기능이있어
convolutional heirs and that's going to give us this grid of features
길쌈 상속인과는 우리에게 기능이 그리드를 줄 것
rather than a single feature vector so because these are coming from
오히려이 때문에, 그래서이에서 오는 하나의 특징 벡터보다
convolutional air as you can imagine that maybe the upper left-hand this you
길쌈 공기는 당신이 당신을 그 아마 왼쪽 위를 상상할 수
can think of this as a treaty spatial grid of features and inside each grid
기능의 조약 공간 격자로하고 각 격자 안에이 생각할 수
each point in the grid gives you features corresponding to some part of
그리드의 각 점은 어떤 부분에 해당하는 기능을 제공합니다
the input image so now again will use these these features to initialize the
입력 이미지는 이제 다시 초기화하는이 이러한 기능을 사용합니다
hidden state of our network in some way and now here's where things get
어떤 방법으로 우리의 네트워크의 상태를 숨겨진 물건을 얻을 경우 지금 여기
different now we're going to use our hidden state to compute not a
다른 이제 우리는하지 계산하기 위해 우리의 숨겨진 상태를 사용하는거야
distribution over words but instead a distribution over these different
단어를 통해 분배하는 대신 서로 다른 이상 배포
positions in the in our convolutional feature map so again this is this would
우리의 길쌈 기능지도에서의 위치 때문에 다시이 것입니다
probably be implemented with may be awfully connect with maybe and a fine
아마도 몹시 아마와 잘 연결 수로 구현 될 수
layer or two and then some soft max to give you a distribution but we just end
층 또는 두 후 일부 소프트 맥스는 당신에게 메일을주고 있지만, 우리는 단지 종료
up with this al dimensional vector giving us a probability distribution
우리에게 확률 분포를주는이 알 차원 벡터 최대
over these different locations and our input and now we take this probability
서로 다른 위치와 우리의 입력을 통해 지금 우리는이 확률을
distribution and actually use it to read to wait to get a weighted sum of those
분포는 실제로 이들의 가중 합을 얻기 위해 기다리는 읽을 사용
feature vectors at the different points in our in our grade so once we take this
우리 학년 우리는이 걸릴 그래서 일단 우리의 다른 점에 특징 벡터
weighted combination of features that takes our grid and summarizes it down to
우리의 그리드를 받아 그것을 아래로 요약 기능의 가중 조합
a single factor there and this this sort of disease vector summarizes the input
이 하나의 요인과 질병 벡터의이 이런 종류의 입력을 요약
image in some way and due to the different types do to do to this
다른 유형의 몇 가지 방법으로 인해 이미지가 이것에 어떻게 할
probability distribution it gives the network the capacity to focus on
확률 분포는 네트워크를 집중하는 능력을 준다
different parts of the image as it goes so now this this weighting factor that's
이미지의 다른 부분은 지금의이이 가중치를 간다
produced from the input features gets fed together with the first word and now
입력 기능에서 생성 이제 첫 번째 단어와 함께 공급됩니다
when we make a recurrence in a recurrent network we actually have three and parts
우리가 재발 네트워크의 재발을 할 때 우리는 실제로 세와 부품이
we have our previous hidden state we have this attended feature vector and we
우리는 우리의 이전의 숨겨진 상태를 가지고 우리는이 참석 특징 벡터가 우리
have this first word and now all of these together are used to produce our
생산이 함께 사용되는 모든 지금이 첫 번째 단어가 우리의
new hidden state and now from this hidden state we're actually going to
새로운 숨겨진 상태와 지금이 숨겨진 상태에서 우리가 실제로 갈거야
produce two outputs we're going to produce another a new distribution over
우리는 다른 새로운 유통을 통해 생산하는거야 두 개의 출력을 생성
the locations and our input image and we're also going to reduce our standard
위치와 우리의 입력 이미지와 우리는 또한 우리의 표준을 감소시키는거야
distribution over words so these are probably be implemented as just a couple
이 때문에 단어 이상 분포는 아마 몇으로 구현 될 수있다
of active layers on top of the hidden states and now this process repeats so
의 활성 숨겨진 상태의 상단에 레이어 이제이 과정은 그렇게 반복
given this new probably distribution we go back to the input feature grand
우리는 입력 기능 그랜드​​으로 돌아가 새로운 아마도 분포를 부여
and come to a new summarization vector for the invention take take that dr.
그 닥터을 본 발명에 대한 새로운 요약 벡터에 걸릴 온다.
together with the next word in the sentence to compute the New Haven
함께 뉴 헤이븐을 계산 문장의 다음 단어
State's produce ok so that spoiled a little bad but I'm by Ben will actually
국가의 생산은 확인 그래서 조금 나쁜 버릇이 있지만 벤에 의한 것 사실이야
repeat this process overtime to generate captions yeah so the question is how
캡션을 생성하는이 프로세스 초과 근무를 반복 그래 그래서 질문은 어떻게
where does this feature good come from and the answer is when you're when
여기서이 기능 좋은에서 오는가 당신이 때있을 때 대답은
you're doing and Alex that for example you have con- wanna come to country
당신은 예를 들어 당신이 CON- 싶어 나라에 와서 가지고 일을하고 알렉스있어
Kanpur come by and by the time you get to come five the shape of that tensor is
칸 푸르는로 와서 시간으로 다섯을 그 텐서의 형상이되어 온에 도착
now something like seven by seven by five hundred and twelve so that
그래서 오백열둘에 의해 일곱으로 칠 등 지금 뭔가
corresponds to a seven by seven spatial grid over the input and each grid
입력 및 각 격자를 통해 일곱 일곱하여 공간 격자에 해당
position that's a 512 dimensional feature vector so those are just pulled
그래서 사람들은 그냥 뽑아되는 512 차원의 특징 벡터의 위치
out of one of the convolutional there is a network question
길쌈 중 하나에서 네트워크 문제가있다
so the question is about this probably distributions so we're actually
우리가 실제로있어 그래서 이렇게 질문이 아마 분포에 관한 것입니다
producing two different probability distributions at every time step the
모든 시간에 두 개의 서로 다른 확률 분포를 생성하면 단계
first one of these d vectors and blue so those are probably distribution over
이 D 벡터의 하나의 제와 푸른 그래서 그 유통을 통해 아마
words in your vocabulary like we did in normal image captioning and also at
어휘 단어 우리가 정상적인 이미지 캡션과도에서처럼
every time step will produce a second probability distribution over these
때마다 단계는이 이상의 두 번째 확률 분포를 생성합니다
locations in the end in the input image that are telling us where we want to
우리가 원하는 위치를 입력 이미지의 끝에 위치는 우리에게 말하고되는
look next time step sis is actually quite right so if you're just tuning to
단계 동생이 아주 적합한 단지로 조정하고, 그래서 만약 실제로 다음에 봐
ups and then as a quiz wanted to see like what framework you want to use them
업 후 퀴즈 당신이 그들을 사용하고자하는 어떤 프레임 워크를 같이보고 싶었다로
for months and we talked about maybe how r intense would be a good choice for our
개월 동안 우리는 약 어쩌면위한 좋은 선택이 될 것입니다 강렬한 r에 어떻게 이야기를 우리의
tents are flow and I think this qualifies as a crazy are done so I
텐트는 흐름이고 나는 미친이 그렇게 될 때이 자격이 생각 나는
wanted to maybe talk in a little bit more detail how these attention vector
아마 조금 더 자세히 이야기하고 싶었 방법이 주목 벡터
how these summarization doctors get produced so this paper actually talks
이 요약 의사가 생성되는 방식이 문서가 실제로 회담 그래서
about two different methods for generating these factors so the idea as
이러한 요인 때문에 아이디어로서 생성에 대해 두 가지 방법
we saw in the last slide is that we'll take our input image and get this great
우리가 마지막 슬라이드에서 본 우리가 우리의 입력 이미지를 가지고이 위대한를 얻을 수 있다는 것입니다
of teachers coming from one of the convolutional areas in our network and
우리의 네트워크에서 길쌈 영역 중 하나에서 오는 교사와
then each time stop our network will produce this probability distribution
각 시간이 확률 분포를 만들어 우리의 네트워크를 중지
over locations so this would be a full impact of land in a soft maxed out to
위치 이상 그래서 이것은에 끝나가 소프트 토지의 전체 영향 것
normalize it and now the idea is that we want to take these this great feature
그것을 정상화 지금 생각은 우리가이 위대한 기능을 수행 할 것입니다
vectors together with these probability distributions and produce a single
이러한 확률 분포와 함께 벡터와 하나의 생산
d-dimensional factor that summarizes that input image and there's the paper
D-차원 요소 입력 영상 것을 요약하고 용지가있다
actually explores two different ways of solving this problem so the easy way is
실제로 쉬운 방법은 그래서이 문제를 해결하는 두 가지 방법을 탐구
to use what's what they call soft detention so she r Rd dimensional
그녀는 Rd에는 차원 r에 그래서 그들은 부드러운 구금 부르는 것을 사용
vectors eg will just be a weighted sum of all the elements in the grid where
벡터의 예는 그리드 여기서 모든 요소의 가중 합계 것
each factor is just waited by its probably by its predicted probability
각 요소는 바로 아마 그 예측 확률에 의해 그것의에 의해 대기한다
this is actually very easy to implement it sort of a nice as just another layer
이것은 또 다른 층과 같은 종류의 좋은 그것을 구현하기 위해 실제로 매우 간단합니다
in a neural network and these gradients like the derivative of this context
신경망과이 문맥의 유도체 등이 그라디언트
factor with respect are predicted probabilities P is quite nice and easy
대한 요인은 확률을 예측 P는 아주 좋은 쉽습니다
to compute so we can actually trained this thing just using normal gradient
그냥 보통의 구배를 사용하여 우리가 실제로 훈련을 수있는이 일을 계산하기
descent and back-propagation
하강 및 역 전파
but they actually explore another another option for competing this
그러나 실제로이 경쟁하는 다른 또 다른 옵션을 탐험
feature vector and that's something called the heart attention so instead of
특징 벡터 그래서 대신 심장주의라는 그 뭔가
having this weighted sum we might want to select just a single element of that
이 가중 합을 갖는 우리는 단지 하나의 요소를 선택 할 수 있습니다
upgrade to attend to so you might imagine so one simple thing to do is
그래서 당신이 할 수있는 매우 간단한 일을 상상하기에 참석하기 위해 업그레이드
just to pick the elements of the grid with the highest probability and just
단지 확률이 가장 높은 단지로 그리드의 요소를 선택합니다
pull out that feature vector comp corresponding to that part tax position
그 부분 세금 위치에 대응하는 특징 벡터 빌려 당겨
the problem is now if you think about in this card max in this park next case if
이 공원 옆 경우 경우에이 카드가 최대에 대해 생각하면 문제는 지금
you think about this derivative the derivative with respect to our
당신에 대한이 파생 상품에 대한 미분을 생각하는 우리의
distribution P
배포 P
it turns out that this is not very friendly for backpropagation anymore so
이것이 그래서 더 이상 역 전파에 대한 매우 친절 아니라고 밝혀
imagine in our next case if I suppose that a that P A or actually the largest
내가 실제로 가장 큰 그 PA한다고 가정 또는 경우에 우리의 다음 경우 상상
element and our input and now what happens if we change pH just a little
요소와 우리의 입력과 우리가 조금의 pH를 변경하는 경우 지금 무슨 일이
bit rate so if he is the architects and then we just jiggle the probability
비트 레이트는 그래서 만약 그가 건축가이며, 우리는 확률을 가볍게 흔들다
distribution just a little bit NPA will still be the architects so we'll still
유통 조금 NPA는 여전히 건축가가 될 것입니다 그래서 우리는 여전히거야
select the same factor from the input which means that actually the derivative
실제로 미분을 의미하는 입력에서 동일한 요소를 선택
of this factor is easy with respect are predicted probabilities is going to be 0
이 요소의 대해 쉽게 예측할 확률은 0이 될 것입니다있다
almost everywhere so that's that's very bad week now we can't really use
지금 우리가 정말 사용할 수 없습니다 거의 모든 곳에서 그, 그래서 그것은 아주 나쁜 주입니다
backpropagation anymore to train this thing so it turns out that they propose
그들이 제안하는 것을 알 수 있도록 역 전파 더 이상이 일을 훈련합니다
another method based on reinforcement learning to actually train the model in
강화 학습을 기반으로 또 다른 방법은 실제의 모델을 학습합니다
this context where you want to select a single element but that's a little bit
당신이 원하는 이러한 상황은 단일 요소를 선택하지만 약간의
more complex so we're not gonna talk about that in this lecture but just be
더 복잡한 우리는이 강의에서 그것에 대해 않을거야 말거야하지만 단지 수 있도록
aware that that is something that you'll see the difference between soft
그건 당신이 부드러운의 차이를 볼 수 있습니다 뭔가 알고 있음
attention and heart attention where you actually pick one so now we can look at
실제로 지금 우리가 볼 수 하나를 선택 관심과 심장주의
some some pretty results from this model so since we're actually generating a
우리가 실제로 발생하고 그렇게 때문에이 모델에서 일부 꽤 결과
probability distribution over grid locations every time stop we can
그리드 위치 우리가 할 수있는 모든 시간이 정지 이상의 확률 분포
visualize that probability distribution as we generate each word of art are
있습니다 우리는 예술의 각 단어를 생성로서 그 확률 분포를 시각화
generated caption so then this input image that shows a bird both back they
새를 모두 다시 보여줍니다 생성 된 캡션 그럼이 입력 이미지들은
both their heart attention model and her soft attention model in this case both
마음주의 모델 모두이 경우에 그녀의 부드러운주의 모델 모두
produced the caption a bird flying over a body of water period
캡션에게 물주기의 몸에 비행 조류를 생산
and for these two models they visualize what that probability distribution looks
이 두 모델들은 무엇을 그 확률 분포의 모양을 시각화
like these two different models so the top shows the soft attention so you can
이 두 가지 모델처럼 상단은 부드러운주의를 할 수 있도록 보여줍니다 있도록
see that it's sort of diffuse since it's averaging probabilities from every
이 모든에서 확률을 평균이기 때문에 그것은 일종의 확산있어 볼
location and image and in the bottom it's just showing the one single element
위치와 이미지 하단에 단지 하나의 요소를 보여주는 것
that it pulled out and it's actually quite nice romantic drama meanings you
그것은 꺼내 실제로 아주 좋은 로맨틱 드라마의 의미를 당신에게 있다는
can see that when the model is especially the soft attention on the top
모델이 특히 부드러운 관심이 상단에있을 때 볼 수 있습니다
i think is very nice results that when it's talking about the bird and talking
나는 새에 대해 얘기하고 얘기 할 때 매우 좋은 결과이다 생각
about flying at sort of focus is right on the bird and then when it's talking
초점 종류의 비행에 대해 새에 적합한 다음이 얘기 할 때
about the water it kinda focuses on everything else so another thing to
물에 대해는 좀 다른 모든 것들 때문에 다른 일에 초점을 맞추고
point out is that it didn't receive any supervision and training time for which
지적 것은 대한 감독 및 교육 시간을받지 않은 것입니다
parts of the image should be attending to it just made up its own mind to
이미지의 일부 단지에 자신의 마음을 만들어에 참석해야한다
attend to those parts based on whatever would help it captured things better and
더 나은 일을 캡처 도움이 무엇 이건을 기반으로 그 부분에 참석
it's pretty cool that we actually get these interpretable results just out of
우리가 실제로 단지에서 이러한 해석 결과를 얻을 수 꽤 멋지다
this captioning task we can look at a couple a couple other results cause
이 자막 작업, 우리는 몇 몇 다른 결과의 원인을 볼 수 있습니다
they're fun we can see that when we have the dog throwing one woman throwing the
우리가 볼 수 그들은 재미있어 그 우리가 던지는 한 여자를 던지고 개를 때
frisbee in the park at Presby talking about the dog at various recognize the
다양한에서 개에 대해 이야기 Presby 공원에서 프리즈는 인식
dog and especially interesting is this guy in the bottom right when it
개, 특히 흥미로운 바로 때를 바닥에서이 사람이다
generates the word trees it's actually focusing on all the stuff in the
그것은 실제로 모든 것들에 초점을 맞추고 단어 나무를 생성
background and not just the giraffe and again these are just coming out with no
배경 다시뿐만 아니라 기린과는 전혀 나오고 있지이
supervision all just based on the caption and ask question yes or the
감독은 모든 단지 캡션을 기반으로 네 질문을하거나
question is whatever when would you prefer hard versus attention so there's
문제는 당신이주의 대 하드 선호하는 경우가 그래서 무엇이다
i think sort of two motivations that people usually give her wanting to even
나는 사람들이 일반적으로 그녀의도에 원하는 줄 것을 일종의 두 동기의 생각
do attention at all in the first place
처음에 전혀 관심을
one of those is just to give nice interminable outputs and I think you get
그 중 하나는 좋은 끝없는 출력을주고 당신이 얻을 생각하는 것입니다
nice interpretable outputs in either case at least theoretically maybe her
두 경우 모두에서 좋은 해석 출력 적어도 이론적으로는 아마도 그녀의
detention think you're wasn't quite as pretty but the other motivation for
구금는 확실히 꽤 있지만, 다른 동기 부여하지 않았다 것 같아요
using attention is to relieve computational burden especially when you
주의를 사용하여 때를 특히 계산 부담을 완화하는 것입니다
have a very very large and put it might be computationally expensive actually
매우 매우 큰이 있고 실제로 계산 비용이 많이들 수 있습니다 넣어
process that whole input on every time step and it might be more efficient
각 시간 단계에서 그 전체의 입력을 처리하고 더 효율적일 수도
computationally if we can just focus on one part of the input at each time step
우리는 단지 각 시간 단계에서 입력 한 부분에 초점을 맞출 수 계산하는 경우
only process a small subset pretends that so with soft attention because
단지 작은 부분 집합 척 처리가 부드러운 관심 때문에 너무
we're doing this sort of averaging over all positions we don't get any
우리는 우리가 어떤을하지 않는 모든 포지션에 걸쳐 평균 이런 종류의 일을하고
computational savings are still processing the whole input on every time
계산 저축은 여전히​​ 모든 시간에 전체 입력을 처리하는
step but with heart attention we actually do get a computational savings
단계하지만 마음의 관심과 우리는 실제로 계산 절감 효과를 얻을 수 있습니까
since were explicitly pic picking out some small subset of the input so I
명시 적으로 I 있도록 입력의 일부 작은 부분 집합을 따기 (pic)의 한 사람
think that's that's the big benefits also her detention takes reinforcement
또한 그녀의 구금이 강화됩니다 즉 그 큰 혜택을의 생각
learning and expand CRN makes you look smarter that's kind of question yeah so
학습과 CRN 당신이 똑똑 그 종류의 그래 그래서 질문있어 보이게 확장
the question is how does this work at all and I think the answer is it's
문제는 모든에서이 작업을 수행하는 방법을 내가 대답은 그것의 생각
really learning sort of correlation structures in the input right that it's
정말 그것의 입력 오른쪽 상관 관계 구조의 종류를 학습
seen many examples of images with dogs and it's a many sentences with dogs but
강아지와 이미지의 많은 예를 보지하고 강아지와 함께 많은 문장입니다 만
for those different images with dogs the dogs tend to appear in different
강아지와 함께 그 다른 이미지의 개는 다른에 표시하는 경향이
positions in the input and I guess it turns out through the optimization
입력의 위치와 나는 그것이 최적화를 통해 밝혀 같아요
procedure that actually putting more weight on the places where the dog
절차 실제로 장소에 더 무게를 두는 경우 개
actually exists actually helps the captioning task in some way so I don't
실제로 실제로 존재 그렇게하지 ​​않도록 몇 가지 방법으로 자막 작업을하는 데 도움이
think there's a very very good answer it just it just happens to work also I'm
그냥 그냥도 난 작업 할 일이 아주 아주 좋은 답이 있다고 생각
not sure so obviously these are pictures from a figure these are figures from a
확실하지 그래서 분명이 다음이에서 수치입니다 인물의 사진입니다
paper not like random results so I'm not sure how good it works on random images
그것은 임의의 이미지를 어떻게 작동하는지 잘 잘 모르겠어요 그래서 논문은 임의의 결과가 마음에 들지
but another thing to really point out about this especially this model a soft
하지만 다른 점은 정말이 특히이 모델 소프트에 대한 지적합니다
detention is that it's sort of constraints to this fixed grid from the
구금은 제약 조건의 종류가에서이 고정 된 격자 점이다
convolution feature map that these like we get more getting these nice diffused
우리 같은 이들보다이 좋은이 확산 점점 얻을 컨볼 루션 기능지도
looking things but those are just sort of like blurring out this this
일을 찾고 있지만, 사람들은 그저이이 밖으로 흐리게처럼
distribution and the model does not really have the capacity to look at
분포 모델 실제로보고 할 능력이없는
arbitrary regions of the input it's only allowed to look at these are fixed grid
입력의 임의의 영역 만이 고정 그리드 볼 수있어
regions
지역
I should also point out that this idea of soft attention was not really
또한 부드러운 관심이 아이디어는 정말 아니라고 지적한다
introduced in this paper I think the first paper that really had this notion
본 논문에서 소개 난 정말이 개념을 가지고 있었던 첫 번째 논문을 생각한다
of soft attention came from machine translation so here it's a similar
부드러운 관심은이 유사 그래서 여기에 기계 번역에서 온
motivation that we want to take some input sentence here in Spanish and then
우리는 다음 스페인어, 여기에 몇 가지 입력 문장을하려는 의욕
produce an output sentence in English and this would be done with recurrent
영어로 출력 문장을 생성하고이 재발와 함께 할 것
neural network sequence to sequence model where we would first read in our
우리는 먼저 판독 할 시퀀스 모델 신경망 시퀀스 우리
input sentence with a recurrent network and then generate an output sequence is
입력 재발 네트워크와 문장하고는 출력 시퀀스가​​ 생성
very similar to that as we would in captioning
우리는 자막에서와 같은 매우 유사
but in this paper they wanted to actually have attention over the inputs
그러나이 논문에서 그들은 실제로 입력을 통해 관심을 가지고 싶어
intense as they generated their sentence so the exact mechanism as a little bit
강렬한 그들은 조금으로 정확한 메커니즘 때문에 자신의 문장을 생성 된
different but the intuition has the same that now when we generate this first
다른 그러나 직관은 지금 우리가 처음이를 생성 할 때 같은있다
word my we want to compute power distribution not over
말씀은 우리를 통해 전력 분배를하지 계산하려는의 나
regions in an image but instead over words in the input sentence so we're
이미지의 대신 우린 있도록 입력 문장에서 단어를 통해 지역
gonna get a distribution that hopefully will focus on this first word in Spanish
거 희망을 스페인어로이 첫 번째 단어에 초점을 맞출 것이다 분포를 얻을
sentence and then we'll take some pictures from each word and then relate
문장, 그리고, 우리는 각 단어의 일부 사진을 촬영 한 후 관련이 있습니다
them and feed them back into the next time step in this process would repeat
이를 반복 것이이 프로세스의 다음 단계로 궤환
at every time step up the network so this idea of soft detention is very
모든 시간에 너무 부드러운 구금이 아이디어는 매우있는 네트워크를 단계
easily applicable not only to image capturing but also to machine
이미지 캡처에뿐만 아니라 기계뿐만 아니라 쉽게 적용
translation question the question is how do you do this for a variable-length
번역 질문은 질문은 가변 길이에 대해이 작업을 수행 할 방법입니다
sentences and that's something I glossed over a little bit but the idea is you
문장 그리고 내가 조금 이상 호도 뭔가하지만 아이디어는 당신입니다
use what's called content based addressing so for the image captioning
이미지 캡션에 대한 그래서 주소 내용이라고 기반으로 무엇을 사용
we all know ahead of time that there is this fixed maybe seven by seven grid so
우리 모두는이 일곱 그리드에 의해 아마 일곱이 고정되어 있는지 미리 알 수 있도록
we just produce a probability distribution directly instead in this
우리는 단지이 직접하는 대신 확률 분포를 생성
model as the encoder reads the input sentence it's producing some vector that
인코더와 같은 모델은 일부 벡터를 생성있어 입력 된 문장을 읽는
encodes that each word in the input sentence so now in the decoder instead
인코딩이 디코더에서 지금 입력 문장의 각 단어 대신
of directly producing a probability vector a probability distribution its
의 직접 확률 분포 확률 벡터를 생성 그것
way to spread out sort of a vector that will get dot product it with each of
방법은 각각과 내적을 얻을 것이다 벡터의 종류를 확산하기
those encoded vectors and the input and then those top products get used to get
그 코드 벡터와 입력 한 다음 그 위에 제품을 얻을 익숙해
renormalized and converted to a distribution
재 정규화 및 분포로 변환
so this idea of soft detention is actually pretty easy to implement and
그래서 부드러운 구금이 아이디어를 구현하기 꽤 용이하고
pretty easy to train so it's been very popular in the last year or so and
꽤 훈련하기 쉬운 그래서 작년 정도에 매우 인기가있어와
there's a whole bunch of papers that apply this idea of soft attention to a
A와 부드러운 관심이 아이디어를 적용 논문의 전체 무리가있다
whole bunch of different problems so there have been a couple papers looking
다른 문제의 전체 무리보고 몇 논문이 있었다 있도록
at soft detention for machine translation as we saw there have been a
우리가 본대로 기계 번역 소프트 구금에서이되어왔다
couple papers that actually want to do
실제로하고 싶은 몇 가지 서류
speech transcription where they read in an audio signal and then I'll put the
그들은 오디오 신​​호에 읽은 다음 나는 놓을 게요 음성 녹음
words in English so there's been a couple papers that use soft attention
영어 단어는 너무 부드러운 관심을 사용하는 몇 가지 서류가되었습니다
over the input audio sequence to help with that task weeks there's been at
해당 작업 주에 도움이 입력 오디오 시퀀스를 통해 거기에있었습니다
least one paper on using soft attention for video captioning so here you read in
당신이 읽을 그래서 여기에 동영상 캡션 소프트 관심을 사용하는 방법에 적어도 하나의 종이
some sequence of frames and then you output some sequence of words and you
프레임의 일부 순서와 단어와 당신의 다음 출력을 어떤 순서
want to have a tension over whether the frames of the input sequence as you're
가있는 한, 입력 시퀀스의 프레임인지를 통해 장력을 갖도록 할
generating your caption you could see that maybe for this little video
캡션을 생성하는 당신은 아마이 작은 비디오 것을 볼 수 있었다
sequence they output someone is trying to fish in a pot and when they generate
시퀀스들은 출력 누군가가 냄비에 물고기 위해 노력하고 때 생성된다
the words someone actually attend much more to this second frame in the video
단어 누군가가 실제로 비디오에서이 두 번째 프레임에 많은 참석
sequence and when they generate the word frying attends much more to this last
순서 그들은 단어 튀김이 마지막에 더 많은 참석 생성 할 때
element in the video sequence there have also been a couple papers for this task
비디오 시퀀스의 요소는이 작업에 대한 몇 가지 서류가 있었다
of question answering so here you the setup is that you read in a natural
당신에게 그래서 여기에 설정을 응답 질문을하면 자연에서 읽을 수 있다는 것입니다
language question and you also read an image and image and the model needs to
언어 질문 당신은 또한 이미지와 이미지를 읽고 모델에 필요
produce an answer about that question
그 질문에 대한 답을 생산
produced the answer to that question in natural language so and there been a
그래서 자연 언어에서 그 질문에 대한 답을 생산하고 거기
couple papers that explore the idea of spatial attention over the image in
이미지를 통해 공간주의의 아이디어를 탐구 커플 논문
order to help with this problem of question answering another thing to
또 다른 일을 응답 질문이 문제를 돕기 위해
point out is that some of these papers have great games so there was a
지적하는 것은이 있었다, 그래서이 논문의 일부는 좋은 게임을 가지고있다
show-and-tell there was show attendant I'll there was less than a tenth and
보여 앤 알려 쇼 교환이 있었다 나는거야 거기 십분 미만
spell
주문
and this one is asked to attend an answer so I I really enjoy about
II 정말 약 즐길 수 있도록이 하나 답변을 참석하도록 요청
creativity with naming I'm just on this line of work and this idea of soft
나는이 작업 줄에 불과 해요 이름으로 창의력과 부드러운의이 아이디어
detention is pretty easy to implement so a lot of people have just uploaded two
구금 그래서 많은 사람들이 두을 업로드 구현하기 매우 쉽다
tons of tasks but remember we saw this problem with this sort of implementation
하지만 작업의 톤은 우리가 구현 이러한 종류의와 함께이 문제를보고 기억
of soft attention and that's that we cannot attends to arbitrate regions in
부드러운 관심의 그것은 우리가 지역을 중재하기 위해 참석 할 수 없습니다입니다
the input instead were constrained and can only attend to this fixed grid given
입력 대신 제약하고 만 주어진이 고정 된 그리드에 참석할 수
by the convolutional feature map so the question is whether we can overcome this
길쌈 기능지도에 의해, 그래서 문제는 우리가 이것을 극복 할 수 있는지 여부입니다
restriction and still attend and attends to arbitrary input regions somehow in a
제한은 여전히​​ 참석하고 어떻게 든 임의의 입력 영역에 참석
different way and I think
내가 생각하는 다른 방법
precursor to this type of work is this paper from Alex graves back in 2013 so
작업 이러한 유형의 전구체는 알렉스에서이 논문은 그래서 2013 년에 다시 무덤이다
here he wanted to read as inputs natural language sentence and then generate as
여기에 그는 같은 입력 자연 언어 문장을 읽고 다음과 같이 생성 원
output actually an image that would be handwriting general like writing out
작성하는 것처럼 일반 필기 될 출력 실제로 이미지
that that sentence in handwriting and the way that he actually has attention
필기에 그 문장과 그가 실제로 관심을 가지고있는 방법이
over this output image in kind of a cool way we're now he's actually predicting
멋진 방법의 종류이 출력 이미지 위에 우리는 지금 그가 실제로 예측하는 것하고
the parameters of some cash and mixture model over the output image and then
그런 다음 출력 영상 이상 현금과 혼합 모델의 파라미터
uses that to actually attend to arbitrate parts of the output image and
실제적으로 출력 영상의 부분을 중재하는 것을 사용하고 참석
this actually works really really well so on the right some of these are
이 사실은 이들 중 일부는 오른쪽에 정말 잘 그래서 정말 작동
actually written by people and the rest of them were written by him by his
실제로 사람들에 의해 작성하고 나머지는 그의 그를 작성했습니다
network so can you tell the difference between the generated on the real
네트워크는 그래​​서 당신은 현실에서 발생하는 차이를 알 수 있습니다
generating I couldn't so it turns out that the top one is real and he's
내가 할 수 없습니다 생성하는 그래서 상단 하나는 진짜 그가 있다고 밝혀
bottomed for all generated by the network
네트워크에 의해 생성 된 모든 바닥
yeah maybe maybe the real ones have more variance between the letters or
그래 어쩌면 어쩌면 진짜 기적은 문자 나 사이에 많은 차이가
something like that but these results work really well and actually he has an
그런 일하지만, 이러한 결과는 정말 잘 작동 실제로 그는이
online demo that you can go on and try that runs in your browser you can just
당신이 가서 그 방금 할 수있는 브라우저에서 실행하려고 할 수있는 온라인 데모
type in words and will generate the handwriting for you that's kind of fun
단어를 입력하고 재미 종류의 당신을위한 필기를 생성합니다
another another paper that we saw already is draw that that sort of takes
우리가 이미 본 다른 또 다른 종이 종류의 소요가 그 그릴입니다
this idea of arbitrary detention over and then extends it to a couple more
다음을 통해 임의 구금이 아이디어는 몇 가지 더로 확장
real-world problems not just handwriting generation so one task they consider is
실제 세계의 문제는 세대가 그래서 그들은 고려 하나의 작업은 필기하지
image classification here we want to classify these digits but in the process
이미지 분류는 여기에 우리가하지만 그 과정에서이 숫자를 분류 할
of classifying we're actually going to attend to arbitrate regions of the input
분류의 우리는 실제로 입력 영역을 중재하기 위해 참석거야
image in order to help with this classification task so this is this is
이 분류 작업에 도움하기 위해 이미지 그래서 이것은이입니다
kind of cool it sort of learns on its own but it needs to attend to these
가지가 종류의 자체 학습 냉각하지만이 참석해야
digits in order to help with image classification and withdrawn they also
순서대로 숫자는 영상 분류에 도움이 또한 철회합니다
consider the idea of generating arbitrary output images with a similar
유사한과 임의 출력 이미지를 생성하는 개념을 고려
sort of motivation as the handwriting generation where we're gonna have
우리가 가지고있는거야 필기 생성과 같은 동기 부여의 종류
arbitrary attention over the output image and just generate this output on
출력 이미지를 통해 임의의 관심은 단지에이 출력을 생성
my bed and I think we saw this video before but it's really cool so this is
내 침대와 나는 우리가 전에이 동영상을 본 것 같아요하지만이 그래서 정말 멋지다
the draw network from my mind so you can see that here we're gonna do it we're
당신이 여기에서 우리는거야 볼 수 있도록 내 마음에서 무승부 네트워크는 우리가있어 그것을 할
doing a classification task sort of learns to attend to arbitrate regions in
분류 작업을하는 것은 일종의에서 영역을 중재에 참석하기 위해 배운다
the input and when we generate we're going to attend to arbitrate regions in
우리는 우리가 지역을 중재하기 위해 참석거야 생성 입력 할 때
the output to actually generate these digits so it can generate multiple
그것은 다수 생성 할 수 있도록 출력은 실제로 이러한 숫자를 생성
digits at a time and it can actually generate these these house number these
한 번에 숫자와 실제로이이 집 번호 다음를 생성 할 수 있습니다
house numbers so this is really cool and as you can see you like the region it
집 번호는 그래서 이것은 정말 멋진 당신이 볼 수 있듯이 당신은이 지역을 좋아한다
was attending to was actually growing and shrinking overtime and sort of
실제로 종류의 성장과 초과 근무 축소되었다 참석했다
moving continuously over the image and it was definitely not constrained to a
이미지 위에 연속적으로 이동 그것은 확실히에 구속되지 않았습니다
fixed grid like we saw with show attendant tell so the way that this
우리와 같은 고정 된 그리드이되도록하는 방법을 알려 쇼 교환 보았다
paper works is a little bit a little bit weird and some follow-up work from deep
작동 종이 조금 조금 이상하고 깊은 일부 후속 작품입니다
mind I think actually was more clear and why is the sky all my focus is all ok
내 모든 초점은 모든 괜찮 좀 더 분명 왜 하늘은 실제로 생각하는 마음
right so there's this follow-up paper that take that uses a very similar
바로 그래서 매우 유사한을 사용 걸릴이 후속 논문이있다
mechanism attention called special transport networks but i think is much
기구의 관심은 특별한 전송 네트워크라고하지만 난 많은 생각
easier to understand
이해하기 쉽게
and and presented in a very clean way so the idea is that we want to have this
그리고 매우 깨끗한 방법으로 제시 한 아이디어는 우리가 갖고 싶어한다는 것입니다 수 있도록
input image this our favorite bird and then we want to have this sort of
입력 영상이 우리의 마음에 드는 새와 우리는 이런 종류의를 갖고 싶어
continuous set of variables telling us where you want to attend you might
당신은 당신에게 있습니다에 참석하려는 우리에게 말하고 변수의 연속 세트
imagine that we have the corner of the center and width and height of some box
우리가 어떤 상자의 중심과 너비와 높이의 모서리를 상상
of the region we want to attach to and then we want to have some function that
이 지역의 우리에 첨부 할 다음 우리는 몇 가지 기능을 갖고 싶어 그
takes our input image and these continuous attention coordinates and
우리의 입력 영상을 받아 이러한 지속적인 관심 좌표
then produces some fixed size output and we won't be able to do this in a
다음 몇 가지 고정 된 크기의 출력을 생성하고 우리는이 작업을 수행 할 수 없습니다
differentiable way so this this seems kinda hard right can you imagine that at
미분 방법은 그래서 이것은 이것은 당신에 그 상상할 수 좀 하드 바로 보인다
least with the idea of cropping then these inputs cannot really be continuous
자르기의 생각과 이상은 다음이 입력은 정말 연속이 될 수 없습니다
they need to be sort of pixel values so our country in two integers and it's not
그들은 두 개의 정수 그렇게 우리 나라 픽셀 값의 정렬을해야하고 그렇지 않아
really clear exactly how we can make this function continuous or differential
우리는이 함수가 연속 또는 차등 할 수있는 방법을 정확하게 정말 선택
and they actually came up with a very nice solution and the idea is that we're
그리고 그들은 실제로 아주 좋은 해결책을 와서 생각은 우리가 걸이다
gonna write down a parametrized function that will map from coordinates of pixels
거 픽셀의 좌표에서지도하는 매개 변수화 기능을 적어
in the outputs to coordinates of pixels in the input so here we're gonna say
그래서 여기에 입력 픽셀의 좌표를 출력에 우리는거야 말거야
that this this upper left upper right-hand pixel any other potential has
이이 왼쪽 오른쪽 상단 픽셀 것을 다른 가능성이있다
the coordinates x TYT in the output and we're going to check compute these
좌표는 출력에 TYT을 X와 우리는이를 계산 확인하는거야
coordinates access and white house in the input image using this privatized a
이 민영화를 사용하여 입력 이미지에 액세스 및 백악관 좌표
fine function so that's that's a nice differentiable function that we can
즉 그, 그래서 좋은 함수는 우리가 할 수있는 좋은 미분 가능 함수의
differentiate with respect to these a fine transport accordance then we can
다음 이들에 대해 벌금 전송에 따라을 우리가 할 수있는 차별화
repeat this process and again for maybe the upper upper left-hand pixel in the
에서 아마 상단 왼쪽 상단 픽셀 다시이 과정을 반복
output image we can use this planet rise function to map to the coordinates of
출력 화상 우리의 좌표에 매핑이 행성 상승 기능을 사용하여
the pixel in the input now we can repeat this for all pixels in our output which
입력의 화소 이제 우리는 우리의 출력의 모든 픽셀에 대해이 작업을 반복 할 수있는
gives us something called a sampling grid so the idea is that this will be
생각이 될 것입니다, 그래서 우리에게 샘플링 그리드라는 뭔가를 제공합니다
our output image and then for each pixel in the output the sampling grid tells us
출력의 각 픽셀에 대해 다음 우리의 출력 이미지와 샘플링 그리드는 우리에게 알려줍니다
where in the input that pixel should come from and how many guys taking a
여기서 입력에 픽셀에서 온해야 얼마나 많은을 복용하는 사람
computer graphics course not many so this looks left looks kinda like texture
컴퓨터 그래픽 과정 많지 않은이 왼쪽에 보이는 질감처럼 좀 보인다 그래서
mapping doesn't it so they take this idea from texture mapping in computer
그들은 컴퓨터에 텍스처 매핑에서이 아이디어를 취할 수 있도록 매핑은하지 않습니다
graphics and just use by linear interpolation to compute the output once
단지 선형 보간하여 사용하고 그래픽 한 번 출력을 계산하기
we have the sampling grid
우리는 샘플링 그리드가
so now what now that we have now this now this allows our networked actually
그래서 우리가 가지고 이제 지금 무슨 일이 지금이 지금이 실제로 우리의 네트워크를 할 수 있습니다
attends to arbitrate parts of the input and a nice differentiable way where our
입력과 좋은 미분 방법의 일부를 중재하기 위해 참석 우리
network will now just predict these transforming coordinates pana and that
지금 바로이 변형을 예측합니다 네트워크는 PANA 것을 좌표
will allow the whole thing to attend to arbitrate regions of the input image so
그래서 입력 영상의 영역을 중재에 참석하기 위해 전체를 수
they put this thing altogether into a nice little self-contained module that
그들은 좋은 작은 독립적 인 모듈에 모두이 일을 넣어 그
they call a special transformer so the spatial transformer receives some input
공간 변압기가 어떤 입력을 수신 그래서 그들은 특별한 변압기를 호출
which you can think of as a as our raw input image and then actually runs this
우리의 원시 입력 이미지로하고 다음 실제로 실행 당신이 생각할 수있는
small localisation network which could be a small fully connected network or a
작은 완전히 연결 네트워크 또는 될 수있는 작은 현지화 네트워크
very shallow convolutional network and this this localization network will
매우 얕은 길쌈 네트워크 및이이 현지화 네트워크의 뜻
actually produces as output these a plan transform coordinates data now these
실제로 지금이 출력이 좌표 데이터를 변환 계획으로 생산
affine transform coordinates will be used to compute a sampling grid so now
아핀 변환 좌표는 이제 샘플링 그리드를 계산하는데 사용될
that we've predicted these at misshapen transformed from the localisation
우리가보기 흉한에서 이러한 예측 한 것을 국산화로 변환
network we map each pixel in the output the coordinates of each pixel in the
우리는 네트워크의 출력에서​​의 각 화소의 좌표를 각각의 화소를 매핑
output back to the input and this is a nice smooth differentiable function now
출력을 다시 입력이 지금은 좋은 부드러운 미분 함수
once we have the sampling grid we can just applied by linear interpolation to
우리가 샘플링 그리드를 일단 우리는 단지에 선형 보간에 의해 적용 할 수 있습니다
compute the values in the pixels of the output and if you if you think about
출력의 픽셀 값을 계산하고 경우에 당신이 생각하는 경우
what this thing is doing it's clear that every single part of this network is one
어떻게이 일을하고있는 것은이 네트워크의 모든 단일 부품이 하나라는 것을 분명
continuous and two differential so this thing can be managed jointly without any
이 일이 어떤없이 공동으로 관리 할 수​​ 있도록 지속적이고 두 개의 차동
crazy reinforcement learning stuff which is quite nice although 11 sort of
11 종류의 비록 아주 좋은 미친 강화 학습 물건
caveats know about bilinear sampling if you know how by linear sampling works it
당신이 선형으로 샘플링이 그것을 어떻게 작동하는지 알고있는 경우주의 사항은 바이 리니어 샘플링에 대해 알고
means that every pixel in the output is going to be a weighted average of four
출력의 각 화소가 넷의 누적 평균가는 것을 의미
pixels and the input so those gradients are actually very local so this is
픽셀과 입력 그래서 그 기울기는 실제로 매우 로컬 그래서 이것은이다
continuous and differentiable a nice but I don't think you get a whole lot of
연속과 미분 멋진하지만 난 당신의 전체 많이 얻을 생각하지 않습니다
gradient signal through the third the bilinear sampling but once you have this
세 번째 바이 리니어 샘플링을 통해하지만 당신이이 한 번 기울기 신호
special this nice special transport module we can just insert it into
특별이 ​​좋은 특수 전송 모듈 우리는 단지에 삽입 할 수 있습니다
existing networks to sort of let them learn to attend two things so they
네트워크에 존재하는 일종의 그들이 있도록 두 가지 참석을 배울 수 있도록
consider this classification task very similar to the drop paper where they
드롭 종이와 매우 유사이 분류 작업을 고려 어디
want to classify these warped versions of amnesty Jets so they actually
실제로 그들이 그렇게 사면 제트기의 이러한 변형 된 버전을 분류 할
consider several other
여러 가지 다른 생각
more complicated transforms not just he's a fine transformants you can also
더 복잡한 변환하지 당신은 또한 할 수있는 단지 그가의 좋은 형질 전환
imagine that that's the mapping from your output pixel spektr in pixels on
그의 화소에서 출력 픽셀 SPEKTR에서 매핑의 상상
the previous flight we showed an affine transform but they also consider
우리는 아핀을 보였다 이전의 비행 변환 그러나 또한 고려
projective transforms and also a thin plate splines but the idea is you just
사영 변환도 얇은 판 스플라인하지만 아이디어는 당신에게 그냥
want to some private rise and differentiable function and you could go
일부 민간 상승과 미분 가능 함수를 원하고 당신은 갈 수
crazy with that part so here on the left the network is just trying to classify
그래서 여기에 왼쪽 네트워크의 일부 미친 그냥 분류하려고
these digits that are worked so on the left we have different versions of
왼쪽에 이렇게 일을하는이 자리는 우리의 서로 다른 버전이
warped digits on this middle colin is showing these different thin plate
이 가운데 콜린에 변형 된 자리는 서로 다른 얇은 판을 보이고있다
splines that it's using to attend to a part of the image and then on the right
스플라인은 오른쪽에 다음 이미지의 일부에 참석하고 사용하고 있음
shows the output of the spatial transformer model which has not only
뿐만 아니라이 공간 변압기 모델의 출력을 보여줍니다
attended to that region but also on worked at corresponding to those planes
그 영역에 참석뿐만 아니라에 그 비행기에 대응에서 근무
and on the right they're using an app find transpire on the right is using an
오른쪽에 그들은은을 사용하고 오른쪽에 발산 찾기 앱을 사용하고
affine transform not be in place plans you can see that this is actually doing
아핀이 실제로하고있는 것을 볼 수 있습니다 장소의 계획에 있지 변환
more than just attending to the input or actually transforming the input as well
단지 입력에 참석하거나 실제로는 물론, 입력을 변화보다
so for example in this middle column this is a four but it's actually rotated
그래서이 가운데 열에서 예를 들어이는 4이지만 실제로 회전있어
by something by something like ninety degrees so by using this app and
90도 같은으로 뭔가에 의해 때문에이 응용 프로그램을 사용하여 및
transform the network can not only attention before but also rotated into
네트워크 변환 것이 아니라주의 전뿐만 아니라 회전 수로
the proper position for the downstream classification at work and this is all
적절한 직장에서 하류 분류에 대한 위치와이 전부입니다
very cool and i can sort of similar to the soft attention we don't need
아주 멋진 그리고 난 우리가 필요로하지 않는 부드러운 관심을 비슷한의 정렬 할 수 있습니다
explicit supervision it can just decide for itself where it wants to attend in
이에 참석하고 싶어 그냥 스스로 결정할 수 있습니다 명시 적 감독
order to solve problems so these guys have a fancy video as well which is very
이 사람뿐만 아니라 매우있는 멋진 동영상을 가지고 있도록 문제를 해결하기 위해
impressive so this is the transformer module that we just unpacked and here
인상적인 그래서 이것은 우리가 압축을 푼 여기 변압기 모듈입니다
we're actually showing right now this is actually running a classification task
우리는 실제로 지금이 실제로 분류 작업을 실행하는 바로 보여주는 것
but we're varying the input continuously you can see that these different inputs
그러나 우리가 입력을 변경하고 지속적으로 이러한 서로 다른 입력 것을 볼 수있다
the network learns to attends 22 and then actually economic alliances that
네트워크 (22) 다음 실제로 경제 제휴에 참석 배운다 그
digit to sort of a fixed known pose and as we very that input and move it around
자리는 고정 알려진 포즈의 정렬하는 등 우리는 매우 입력이 주변으로 이동
the image the network still does a good job of locking onto the digit and on the
이미지 네트워크는 여전히 자리에와에 잠금의 좋은 일을
right you can see that sometimes it can fix rotations as well right so
바로 당신은 때때로 잘 그래서뿐만 아니라 회전을 해결할 수 있음을 알 수
here on the left were actually rotating that digit and the network actually
여기 왼쪽에 실제로 그 자리 실제로 네트워크를 회전했다
learns to on rotate the debt and economic life the polls and again both
다시 모두 부채와 경제 생활 투표와 회전 배운다
with a friend transforms or thin plate splines this is using even crazier
친구가 변형 또는 얇은 판 스플라인이도 미쳤 사용하여
warping with projected transports she can see that it does a really good job
예상 전송으로 휘게 그녀는 정말 좋은 일을 볼 수 있습니다
of learning to attend and also its own work and they do quite a lot of other
의 또한 자신의 작품에 참석하고 학습하고 다른 꽤 많이 할
experiments instead of classification they learn to add together to work
대신 분류의 실험은이 일을 함께 추가 학습
digits which is kind of weird task but it works so their network is receding
가지 이상한 일이다하지만 그렇게 네트워크가 후퇴되어 작동 자리
two inputs as to input images and I'll put the sum and it burns and even know
두 개의 입력 입력 영상에 관해서는 나는 합계를 놓을 게하고 화상과 알지도
this is kind of a weird task it learns that it needs to attend and on work
이 그것이 참석하고 작업에 필요가 있음을 알게 이상한 작업의 종류
those images so this is during optimization writes this is a test
이 때문에 그 이미지 최적화이 테스트입니다 기록 중입니다
called co-localization the idea is that the network is going to receive two
공동 지역화라는 개념은 두 네트워크를 받으려고한다는 것이다
images of as input maybe two different images all fours and the task is to say
등의 입력 영상 아마 두 개의 서로 다른 이미지 네 다리를하고 작업이 말을하는 것입니다
whether or not those images are the same the same or different and then also
여부 그 이미지는 다음 동일하거나 상이하고, 동일한
local using spatial transformers and end up learning to localize those things as
지역 공간 변압기를 사용하여 같은 것들을 지역화 학습 결국
well as you can see that over the course of training it learns to actually
잘 훈련의 과정을 통해 실제로 배운다 것을 볼 수 있습니다
localize these things very very precisely even when we are closer to the
우리가 가까이있을 때 매우 매우 정밀도이 일을 현지화
image than these networks still learn to localize very very precisely that's a
이러한 네트워크는 여전히 아주 아주 정확하게의 그 지역화하는 법을 배워야보다 이미지
recent paper from deep mind that is pretty cool
꽤 멋진 깊은 마음의 최근 논문
so any other last minute questions about special transformers yeah yeah so the
특수 변압기에 대해 너무 다른 마지막 분 질문 그래 그래서
simple so the question is what is the what is the task of these things are
간단한 때문에 문제는이 일의 작업이 무엇인지 무엇이고 있습니다
doing and at least in the vanilla version is just classification so it
일을하고 바닐라 버전 적어도 그것 때문에 그냥 분류입니다
receives this sort of input which could be warped her cluttered or whatnot and
뒤틀린 될 수있는 입력 이런 종류의 수신 그녀의 어수선 또는 이것 저것하고
all that it needs to do is classified ad budget and sort of in the process of
모두가 할 필요가 그 과정에서 일종의 분류 광고 예산입니다
learning to classify it also plans to attend to the cracked part so that's
또한 그것을 분류하는 학습 즉, 그래서 금이 부분에 참석하기 위해 계획
that's a really cool feature of this this this work right sort of my overview
그건 내 개요이이 작품 오른쪽 정렬이의 정말 멋진 기능입니다
of attention is that we have soft attention which is really easy to
관심의 우리가 정말 쉬운 부드러운 관심을 가지고있다
implement especially in this context of fixed input positions that we just
고정 된 입력 위치의이 맥락에서 특히 구현하는 우리 단지
produced distributions over and put a man we wait and we feed those those
이상 분포를 생산하고 우리가 기다리는 사람을 넣어 우리는 그 사람들을 먹이
factors back to a network somehow and this is really easy to implement in many
다시 어떻게 든 네트워크 요인이 많은에 구현하기 정말 쉽습니다
different contexts and has been implemented for a lot of different tasks
다른 문맥 및 다른 작업의 많은 구현 된
when you want to attend to arbitrate regions than you need to get a little
당신은 당신이 조금을 얻기 위해 필요한 것보다 지역을 중재하기 위해 참석하고자 할 때
bit fancier and I think spatial transformers is a very very nice elegant
비트 애호가와 나는 공간 변압기 우아한 아주 아주 좋은 생각
way of attending to arbitrate regions in input images there are a lot of papers
입력 이미지의 영역을 중재하기 위해 참석의 방법이 논문 많이 있습니다
that actually work on her detention and this is quite a bit more challenging due
실제로 그녀의 구금 작업이 아주 조금 더 도전 때문이다
to this problem with the gradients so hard attention papers typically use
열심히주의 용지 일반적으로 사용하는 그라디언트이 문제에 대한
reinforcement learning and we didn't really talk about that today so any any
강화 학습은 우리가 정말 그렇게 어떤 임의의 오늘에 대해 이야기하지 않았다
other questions about tension or ok sure
긴장 또는 있는지 확인에 대한 다른 질문
the captioning before we got transformers and yeah those closed
캡션 우리는 변압기를 얻었고, 그래 그 폐쇄하기 전에
captions are produced using this script based thing but in in that network in
캡션에 해당 네트워크에서이 스크립트를 기반으로 일 만에를 사용하여 생산됩니다
particular I think it was a 14 by 14 grid so it's actually quite a lot of
특히 나는 실제로 꽤 많은, 그래서 그것은 (14) (14) 그리드 생각
locations but it it's it's still is constrained to wear it a lot to
여전히 제한되어있어 위치하지만 그것의 그것을 훨씬에 착용
questions about interpolating between soft attention and her detention so yeah
그래서 부드러운 관심과 그녀의 구금 사이에 보간에 대한 질문이 그래
11 thing you might imagine is you train the network in a soft way and then
당신이 상상할 수있는 11 점은 다음 부드러운 방식으로 네트워크를 훈련하고있다
during training you kind of penalize its distribution sharper and sharper and
당신이 종류의 분포가 선명하고 선명하게 처벌 훈련 동안과
sharper and then a test time you just switch over and use her detention
선명하고 테스트 시간은 단지 전환과 그녀의 구금을 사용
instead and I think I can't remember which paper did that but I'm I'm pretty
대신에 나는 내가 그 짓하는 종이 기억할 수 있다고 생각하지만 난 꽤 해요 해요
sure I've seen that idea somewhere but in practice I think training with her
확인은 어디 선가 그 생각을 본 적이 있지만, 실제로 나는 그녀와 함께 훈련 생각
detention tends to work better than the sharpening approach but it's definitely
구금은 선명 방식보다 더 잘 작동하는 경향이 있지만, 확실히이다
something you could try ok if not a question that I think we're done a
뭔가 확인을 시도 할 수 있다면 우리가 일을하고 있다고 생각하지 질문
couple minutes early today so get your homework done
몇 분 일찍 오늘은 그래서 당신의 숙제 완수